<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <ascii>
                                                                                ##
                                                                            ###
                                                                         ###
                                                                    #####
                                                                #######
                                                             ########
                                                         #########
                                                     ###########
                                                 #############
                                             ###############
                                          ################
                                       ##################
                                    ##############   ####
                                  #############       ###
                               ###############        ###
                            ###########   ####        ###
                         ###########       ###        ###
                      ######### ####       ###        ###
                    #######      ##         ##        ###
                 ######          ##         ##        ###
              #####              ##         ##        ###
            ###                  ##         ##        ###
         ###                     ##        ###       #####
      ###                       ####       ###       #####
                                ####       ###        ###
                                ####       ###         #
                                ####       ###
                                ####       ###
                                 ##        ###
                                 ##        ####
                                          #####
                                          #####
                                          #####
                                          #####
                                           ###
    </ascii>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit is Blood.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I am the Blood player! What does that mean?
        </header>
        <body>
            Congratulations, you won the Skaian lottery ticket of bullshit and suffering to earn yourself your
            co-players falling under your jurisdication. Hope you like human interaction, because that is your life now.
            You get to do FUN activities such as dealing with other people's shit for an extended period of time, telling
            people to stop being such childish, pants pooping weenies, and being their personal caretaker, wow, fun.
            Make sure YOU keep their mental health stable, because we ALL know the psyche is such an easy thing to
            understand! You will be blamed for everything un-hinging off the fucking methaporical bullshit rotating door
            that is Sburb. Everything is suffering and pain, and that is in a sense literally what being a Blood player is all
            about. Truly, fuck you and your life. Welcome to Sburb, Hero of Blood, it does not take you kindly, but it is YOUR job to tell it to fuck off.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
    <header>
        Question: My friends are killing each other! I'm supposed to do something, right?
    </header>
    <body>
        Unless you want to fucking doom this timeline, you better haul ass over to where the genocidal cesspool is taking place right the fuck now. Of course, it is at this moment where you are supposed to see two dumbasses fighting it out for something stupid, I don't know and I don't care at this point. You shouldn't either. So while the rest of your friends are kicking back and grabbing their popcorns watching this giant shitshow take place and generally be completely fucking useless, it is now up to you to temporarily give a mild shit about why these dumbasses would rather the other one didn't live. Stand between the two of them and resolve this. Tell them why fucking murdering their friend is probably the worst possible idea they could have possibly produced from their brain. And if you truly are the Blood player, you would have no trouble finding a reason as to why their reason is stupid. Hell, at this point, it shouldn't even surprise you to find yourself inside a torrential mind downpour of reasons as to why their reason is completely fucking retarded. At this point you tell the useless spectators to fuck off. Once they have sufficiently fucked off, it is reccommended that YOU, once again, help them get through their weenie ass problems and help them forgive each other. Ew. But with bowls of chips eaten, bottles of soda empty, and a whole lot of fist bumps shared all around, your work here is done.
    </body>
</section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I brought a dungeon's miniboss down to less than a tenth of its Health Vial, and then... it asked to be my friend? What do I say?
        </header>
        <body>
            As a Hero of Blood, you're very likely to make friends, even in the most unlikely of circumstances. Most generic enemies have a very rare chance of wanting to be your friend, usually if they sense that the situation is dire. Most enemies also have a very small Health Vial. With Minibosses, their health vial is large enough that after a while of smacking them around, they may change their mind about how much they hate you. Having powerful enemies in your party is a massive boon, as most consorts are way to weak to aid you in late game quests. Even if walking around with a three story tall monster seems intimidating, don't pass up on the chance.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: Why is everyone pissing me off so much?! </header> <body> If the Hero of Blood is pissed, it could be for a lot of reasons. Is everyone ignoring you? Is everyone running off, doing their own thing, getting killed? Are they trolling you on purpose? I bet it gets your blood boiling, right? You spend most of their time worrying about everyone else, and what does it get you? HUH? Ingrates. You just gotta keep it together. Without you, they'd all die. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: Why can I see the monster's Health Vials, but no one else can? </header> <body> It's something all Blood Players can do. Your aspect is attuned to the literal pulsation of blood, letting you see just how much of it an enemy has left. Use it to your advantage. Monsters are more succeptible to intimidation when they're low on Health. Some of them might befriend you if you show a little mercy. Or you could be cold-blooded and kill them while you have the chance. Just use your better judgement. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How come some of the monsters I beat up keep following me around?
        </header>
        <body>
            As a Hero of Blood, you'll make some unlikely friends during your session. It comes with the territory. Making connections and getting to know everyone you meet is all a part of your aspect. Most of the generic enemies have small health vials, so it's rare that one of them might befriend you after getting the crap kicked out of it... but with Mini-Bosses, their health vials are large enough that they might change their mind about you after getting smacked around. Don't pass up the opportunity to ally with them. Having some powerful monsters at your disposal can make End-Game strife much easier.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Everyone keeps coming to me for relationship advice. I don't even CARE about Shipping, but they just don't stop. What the hell am I supposed to tell them???
        </header>
        <body>
            Look, chances are, they know that you know EVERYONE. Blood Players are natural confidants, after all. Something about you just feels trustworthy and people like to talk to you, even if they don't know why. It really helps you get a look into who people really are, doesn't it? That said, Shipping is a real touchy subject. You should point them to the nearest Hero of Heart. They'll be way better at it than you could. Your should really just focus on making sure everyone atleast works together and try keep a lid on all that Drama everyone keeps having.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I LITERALLY CAN'T STOP FUCKING SWEARING!!!
        </header>
        <body>
            CONSTANT SWEARING AND CAPSLOCK IS AN INDICATION OF "BLACKBLOOD". IT'S A HIDDEN MECHANIC THAT ANY HERO OF BLOOD CAN TAP INTO. WHEN YOU GET TOO MUCH OF IT, YOU SNAP AND GO A LITTLE BIT ABSOLUTELY FUCKING BERZERK. BE REALLY CAREFUL, IF YOU DON'T HAVE AN OUTLET FOR THIS, YOU MIGHT TURN ON YOUR FRIENDS AND CAUSE A LOT OF BLOODSHED. SWEARING AND CAPSLOCK HELPS VENT THE ANGER, BUT IT'S NOT ENOUGH. GO FIND SOMETHING BIG TO SQUASH WHILE YOU'RE POWERED UP!! THE SOONER YOU BURN OFF THAT UNADULTERED BLACK BLOODED FURY, THE BETTER.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How come I, as a Blood player, have to do a whole bunch of relationship stuffs, while other people get to do all the cool time and space things?
        </header>
        <body>
            Answer: I know, it's bloody boring, isn't it?
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How come I, as a Blood player, have to do a whole bunch of relationship stuffs, while other people get to do all the cool time and space things?
        </header>
        <body>
            Answer: You have metaphysical command over the concept of bonds and attachment, if you don't realize how bullshit that is you clearly aren't a blood player.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Umm... I just got punched into a wall... And I feel... Fine. What's going on?
        </header>
        <body>
            Well, that means, congrats! You're probably not going to die to easily! That's a good thing! And if you're a Blood or Rage player.... Well that's just plain normal, nothing to be worried about.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Blood. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Make sure nobody goes insane.
        </body>
    </section>

</faq>