<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <ascii>                                                              #################
                                                         #############################
             #############                            ####################################
          ####################                    ###########################################
         ##########         ###                 ################################################
        #########             #               ###################################################
       #########                           ########################################################
      #########                         ############################             ####################
     #########                        #########################                       ################
     ##########                     ########################                            ##############
     ###########                  #########################                               ############
      #############            ##########################                                  ###########
       ################################################                                     ##########
         ###########################################     ###############                    ##########
           ######################################    ######################                  #########
             #################################     ###########################               #########
                #########################       ###############################               ########
  ##                 ############             ##################################               #######
   ##                                     ################           ############              ######
    ##                                 ###############                ############             #####
     #####                          ###############                   ############             #####
      ######                   #################                     #############             ####
       ############        ###################                      ##############             ###
           ###############################                         ###############             ##
              #########################                           ################             ##
                     ##########                                   ################             #
                                                                  ################             #
                                                                  ################
</ascii>
    <section>
        <header>
            The Coolest Spots to Fly By!
            
        </header>
        <body>
            Yay, flying! Flying is good and amazing and anyone who says it is bad is wrong and a fuckface. Fuck the
            haters, flight is where it's at! PCHOOOOOOOOOOO!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            How can I get Flight?
        </header>
        <body>
            There's so many ways to fly in Sburb! The easiest way to get flight early to alchemize something with
            rockets. Go find some rocket things or ask the space player for help and you'll be pchooing round till the
            end of time! Vehicles are good too, likes planes and things. Alchemizing these can be a bit harder though.
            Of course, if you get god tier by going to nap on your quest bed, then you can fly about on your own! It's
            so good.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Which is the better dream moon to fly on?
            
        </header>
        <body>
            Both of the dream moons are so good for flying. Both have these really great peaks and valleys formed by the
            spires, and flying along the chain between the main moons and the dreamers moons is so fun. Honestly, I just
            like [redacted] because it's the best, but there's not that much difference between them.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Should I fly between the planets?
            
        </header>
        <body>
            No on so many levels. It's not fun at all to just fly in the void, it gets all boring and it just sucks. Fly
            by terrain, so you have some stuff to mess about with.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            How's the battlefield for flying?
            
        </header>
        <body>
            The battlefield becomes more awesome the more players get in. If you're the only player in, it's barely
            worth the visit. It's only by the fourth player that things get really good. By four players, these strange
            non-euclidean shapes begin to form around the battlefield, which are so fun to fly across. If you have more
            than 8 players in your session, there's no reason not to go fly at the battlefield!
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why should i master gigglesnort.
        </header>
        <body>
            You shouldn't you should speak openly and plainly and never ever trick players revealing to them the transitory nature of physical existance.
            Also it's fun.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section> <header> Question: Why are so many quests on OTHER planets tailored to me? </header> <body> As a player of Breath your quest is a quest of quest, and quest can mean many things. Such as journey. Yours is a quest of motion, you must move ever onwards free as the wind blows. Yours is a quest of freedom, you must not be constrained by a single land even one tailored to you. </body> </section> <section> <header> Question: Am I gonna lose the people close to me? I don't want that! </header> <body> No no, as long as they are close to you then you won’t lose them. Of that I assure you. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What is breath?
        </header>
        <body>
            Spirituality is breath.
            Motion is breath.
            Freedom is breath.
            Quest is breath.
            This is why the wind represents breath as it is pure freedom in motion.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: When do I get to fly?
        </header>
        <body>
            Flying is a representation of freedom and motion allowing you to be free as a bird, to soar above the world apart from yet able to interact with, and you want to know WHEN?
            Echeladder rung 4, when you god tier, Or just alchemize something, jeeze.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Will i get cool points for flying stunts?
        </header>
        <body>
            Fuck no, flying stunts are for posters, if you want cool points you have to do bike stunts and actually you know take risks. When you can fly and not fall it’s not really a stunt is it?
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Do I really need my bonds to others?
        </header>
        <body>
            Most aspects require a kind of balance to achieve their full capacity, as the aspect of freedom and spirituality this is not necessarily true. You can reject the worldly in it’s entirety but like all victories it is a choice you must make for yourself.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why do I feel so distant and unphased by things?
        </header>
        <body>
            Because you are still learning when you should be phased by things, when you understand that you will have the ability to care when needed. Or you left [Eye of the Storm] on after unlocking it, could be either.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What is unreality? Should I mess with it?
        </header>
        <body>
            If reality is positive numbers then unreality is negative numbers. It’s not nothing it’s less than nothing, so much nothing it becomes something.
            It’s not generally recommended to seek unreality if you want to win the game, but if you do Hope and Void players can join you in your quest.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why can’t I become the breeze.
        </header>
        <body>
            Because you still feel the need to not be the breeze.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What the hell is the windy thing?
        </header>
        <body>
            The windy thing is not an action, it is a moment, only when the moment comes will you know what the windy thing is.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Breath. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Dart around and help your coplayers. Don't get attached to them. You'll suck at that.
        </body>
    </section>

</faq>