<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <ascii>
        :(
    </ascii>
    <section>
        <header>
            How Bullshit is Law?
        </header>
        <body>
            I am going to throw you in the slammer if you repeat that joke one more time.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What is the difference between a jail and a slammer?
        </header>
        <body>
            You call it slammer when you're angry.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Help, I can't control the chains!
        </header>
        <body>
            Master the chains or... they will master you. Bwahahahaha. But really, try being more decisive. Practice your movements and stop caring about the movements. Who cares who you're facing, they're just an enemy to be slammered.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Authority Regulators are trying to become my students. What do.
        </header>
        <body>
            You now have a law army. Might want to get a lawyer carapace to lead it. If you don't want one: don't even try, Authority Regulators are hard-coded to venerate the law and you're the Law's champion.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            My friend can't use his specibus and is blaming me for this!
        </header>
        <body>
            Remove the prohibition that's affecting them.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            How do I turn compulsion off?
        </header>
        <body>
            Snap your fingers, tap your foot, whatever. Might also use a compulsion ability to cancel compulsion out.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Law. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Tell others what is illegal and what is to be done. Throw criminals into slammers. Use chains (and ropes) to hold things in place.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What is even this colour scheme.
        </header>
        <body>
            The police tape palette is perfect and I'd rather you stuff your complaints somewhere where sun doesn't shine. Wait, there are no suns in the Medium.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            How does [Sound Judgement] work?
        </header>
        <body>
            You can use it on a player who committed a morally reprehensible crime to ensure that they suffer a Just death. If they are innocent, this ability's backlash will inconvenience you at best and grant you a Just death at worst. Don't worry, it's foolproof when it comes to ignorance - only the user's knowledge counts.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I can't use [Under the Hat].
        </header>
        <body>
            It's a disguise ability which allows you to blend in with the crowd and become invisible to criminals. It's really hard to blend in with consorts and carapacians, unfortunately, and this ability doesn't cover such a discrepancy. Ignore it unless you have more illusion majyyk at your disposal.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>