<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <ascii>

                                           #
                                         ##
                                        ###
                                        #####
                                          ####
                                          #####
                                        ######
                                      #######
                                     #######
                                     #######
                                #     #######      #
                     #          ###   ########   ###          #
                      ###       ##                ##       ###
                       ######     ################     ######
                        ####   ######################   ####
                         ##  ##########################  ##
                           ##############################
                   #####  ################################  #####
                     ##  ##################################  ##
                        ####################################
              ########  ####################################  ########
   ####     #########   ####################################   #########     ####
 ########  ##########   ####################################   ##########  ########
##    #########  #####  ####################################  #####  #########    ##
        ####            ####################################
                         ##################################
                     ##   ################################   ##
                   #####   ##############################   #####
                            ############################
                         ##   ########################   ##
                        ####    ####################    ####
                       ######       ############       ######
                      ###       ##                ##       ###
                     #          ###   ########   ###
                                #      ########
                                        #######
                                        ######
                                       ######
                                      #####
                                      ####
                                      #####
                                        ####
                                          ##
                                         ##
                                        #

    </ascii>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit is Light.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section> <header> Question: I think I found something I shouldn't have. This could really be helpful! </header> <body> You're a Light Player aren't ya? Whatever you found, you need to put it down now and forget about or you will die. I'm not saying it's dangerous, or that it might get you killed, or that it will probably kill you outright. I'm saying YOU WILL DIE. But you're not gonna put it down are you? No you're not, you're a Light Player! Just hope you get lucky and go God Tier afterwards. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question:I have been told by the creatures of my Land that I am 'the Hero of Light',may I inquire what do they mean? </header> <body> Light Player ehh ? As a Friend to one i can tell you some things about Light.From what my Friend ever so eloquently said/typed, the Light Aspect deals with Fortune,Knowledge,Importance mainly,basically all the Cheats ahem, depending on your Class it may manifest itself in differing ways. And that's all my Friend typed/said </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I stepped one inch into a consort village and suddenly everyone stepped out of their homes to greet me? What is this?
        </header>
        <body>
            As a Hero of Light, you will constantly have the metaphorical spotlight on you. This will start off small, such as maybe one or two keen eyed consorts being able to notice you. Eventually, as you grow in power, everyone will be able to see where you are, no matter where you are.

            This of course ruins any chance you have at trying to act stealthy. However, it serves fairly well as a way of keeping enemies distracted. In terms of a role playing game class, the aspect of Light allows you to be a fairly decent tank.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: My friend, who happens to be a Hero of Void, hates my guts! Where did I go wrong?
        </header>
        <body>
            Relax. You've done nothing wrong, it's just that Heroes of Void tend to prefer being in complete darkness. You are constantly radiating light, making it so that you and anyone close to you can be seen from afar. By being close to a Hero of Void, you dispel the darkness around them, causing them to lose their one true power.

            Here is a helpful tip. A flame can dispel the darkness, but the darkness can never dispel a flame. You will forever be the bane of any Hero of Void you come across. This is useful for keeping other players aware of what the Hero of Void is doing, but unless you have a reason to be suspicious, just leave them alone.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Does being a Hero of Light mean I get to shoot lasers?
        </header>
        <body>
            I don't know, have you TRIED to shoot a laser before? In case you're unaware, lasers are totally weaksauce and are in no way shape or form a viable means of combat. Sure, after a while you might cause an uncomfortable amount of heat, but if your goal is to make a target burst into flames, you've got other, way more effective means of doing so.

            Here's one example. Use your powers of light to find whatever object in the vicinity is the most prone to spontaneous combustion. If you're lucky, and being a Hero of Light you will be, it'll be right underneath your enemy's feet. Give it a nudge and watch the damage pile up.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why are all my friends are asking me to help them use a Fraymotif they just purchased?
        </header>
        <body>
            Fraymotif shops are statistically imbalance in favor of giving away free Fraymotifs that include Heroes of Light. Whenever these Fraymotifs are used, you'll notice that despite not being the one to activate them, you end up being the focus. That's what being a Hero of Light is about, after all.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Every few steps I take I come across a rare item. Who's been placing these things everywhere?
        </header>
        <body>
            Oh no, don't be confused. They're not being placed at your feet. This is a video game, after all. It's like a stupid Schrodinger's Cat of pickups. The items don't exist until you look at them. They were always there, but upon observation, it turns out they were rare. Were the items rare all along? Probably. It's just that being a Hero of Light makes you more likely to stumble upon them, and also more likely that the ones you stumble upon are exceedingly rare.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I was doing some fetch quest and then bumped into a consort a few steps away from the one that gave me the mission, and then they dropped the item I needed! Why couldn't they just hand the Consort that item?
        </header>
        <body>
            Lucky you. No really, being a Hero of Light makes you incredibly lucky. If you bother to ask the consort who was holding the item what they were doing standing around, they'll probably tell you about some ridiculously stupid story about how they traveled from one side of your land to the other, losing everything they owned except for that one item, just so they could visit this village and give their friend some soup.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: My friends keep on complaining that I do way too much damage, but when I check my stats, we both have the same amount of Mangrit!
        </header>
        <body>
            When you attack an enemy, watch how they react to your attack. Do you notice them writhe in pain? That's because you're so lucky that all of your attacks end up being critical hits.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: An underling tried to attack me, then it fell into a bottomless pit that wasn't there when I last looked! What happened?
        </header>
        <body>
            You have the aspect of Light to thank for that. Pay closer attention and you would have noticed that the bottomless pit formed only just as the underling reached out to attack you. In short, Light made you incredibly lucky. I mean that in the literal sense of incredible. No one will believe the insanely stupid things that happen when you're around, with good reason too.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I was walking across my land when suddenly I took massive damage! What is this?
        </header>
        <body>
            Being a Hero of Light, you are very, very visible to everything that exists. Get low and look to the horizon, if one even exists on your land. Can you see anything? Is there a tiny speck of black jumping up and down? If yes, then that's probably an underling with access to long ranged weaponry celebrating that it just landed a successful hit. Take this opportunity to make it pay.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Every time I try to solve a puzzle on my land, my first guess is always correct! Are the puzzles broken?
        </header>
        <body>
            Nope, not broken. That's just the aspect of Light giving you a guiding hand. Nine out of ten times, you're going to choose right, and if you choose wrong, it's likely to be on purpose. Have you ever played a game where you had to purposefully fail a mission in order to unlock the next one? It's a lot like that.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Light. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Get money. Screw up others. Make fortune serve you.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>