<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <ascii>
                                       ############
                                #########
                             #######
                          ########
                        ########
           #           #######                        #######
         #            #######                    ##################
        #            #######                ##########################
       ##            ######               ###########            ########
      ##             ######             ########                      #####
     ###             ######           #######                            ###
    ###              ######          ######                                 ##
    ###              ######         ######                                   ##
   ####               #####         ####                                       #
   #####              ######         ###         #############
   ######              ######        ###      ####################
    ######               ######       #     #####        ############
     ######                ######      #  ##                  #########
      #######                  ######  # #                       ########
       ########                        ##  #####                    #######
         #########                   ##  #      #####                 ######
           ###########          #####    ##       ######               ######
              #####################      ###        #####               #####
                  #############          ###         #####               ####
#                                       ####         ######              ####
 ##                                    #####          ######             ####
   ##                                 #####           ######             ###
    ###                            #######            ######             ###
      ####                      #########             ######            ###
        ######              ###########              ######             ##
          ##########################                 ######            ##
             ####################                   ######            ##
                   #######                         ######            #
                                                 #######
                                               #######
                                            ########
                                       #########
                             #############
    </ascii>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit is Space.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Um. Why isn't it letting me do quests with my friends?
        </header>
        <body>
            You're probably the Space Player. That means you're stuck doing bullshit Frog Quests on your own planet, and penalized if you try to step out of line.  If it's any consolation, the Frog Shit IS pretty important. Don't shirk your duties.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Is it just me, or is Space just outright broken?
        </header>
        <body>
            No, it's pretty broken.  We get the detriments of low mobility (which at least KIND of help get the Frog done) but our boost to Alchemy means exactly jack and shit because SBURB is a buggy, half finished piece of shit that doesn't even have an Alchemy Engine.

            Uh. I guess ignore this if you're playing a version that does.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            It won't let me breed the frog?
        </header>
        <body>
            Oh! Shit, my condolences, but I bet you're a Page.  Pages aren't allowed to do ANYTHING without help, and apparently only Knights can help Space players.  Sucks to be you.

            I hear there are versions of SBURB that un-nerf pages of Space, though.

            Oh yeah, and see if you can get any of your friends to maybe Mind control you or something so you'll do it. Apparently that's a work around.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why Frogs?
        </header>
        <body>
            Because tadpoles make a good reproduction metaphor.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I keep trying to breed frogs, but all it does is give me the frog that already exists?
        </header>
        <body>
            That's because you're not messing with the frog, dunkass.   If you don't plan on messing with a frog in the future, then you'll just get the frog itself.

            Instead, what you need to do is have a solid, UNCHANGEABLE NO MATTER WHAT plan to go mess with that frog, later.  That way the frog CAN'T have disappeared, because it clearly exists in the future when you mess with it.

            Also, it shouldn't take a Time Player to figure this out, but this means you have to ACTUALLY GO DO THIS and not just plan to do it.

            I cannot stress this enough.  If you plan on messing with a frog, but then your best friend dies, you still have to go mess with the frog instead of taking the time to mourn. Otherwise you won't have been able to get the paradox slime in the first place.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why is Space about low mobility? Shouldn't we be able to teleport and shit?
        </header>
        <body>
            Yes and No.  Once you're high enough level, depending on your class, you should be able to do some CRAZY shit with Space.  But you're kind of still staying in one spot.  It's everything else that moves.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            The Knight is being an asshole!
        </header>
        <body>
            Deal with it.  Without the Knight you probably won't get the frog breeding done.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: What do I about frogs ? </header> <body> If you are a Space Player,it is VERY IMPORTANT to Breed the Frogs,trust me,it is not a Minigame you can just not do,if you don't do it properly ,the Game will not let you have your Happy Ending. </body> </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Can i just fetch a frog from a doomed timeline?
        </header>
        <body>
            Answer: No, like no you can't. It's doomed, so you'd have to undoom it and that's completely impossible. Then a perfect frog would have to exist in a doomed timeline to begin with, which would never happen. Finally you'd have to completely flub frog breeding in the alpha timeline anyways to even consider such a stupid plan, which you shouldn't do.
            So in summary, If you are seriously asking this question and not just a what if scenario, yes and you always had to.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Space. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Breed the fucking frog. It's the most important sidequest in the game.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>