<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <ascii>                                       ######
                                      ########
                                      ########
                  #                  ##########                  #
                #####                ##########                #####
              ##########            ############            ##########
               ###########    #######################    ############
                ####################################################
                 ##################################################
                 ##################################################
                  ################################################
                 ##################################################
                ####################################################
               ######################################################
 ##################################################################################
 ##################################################################################
####################################################################################
####################################################################################
   ##############################################################################
      ########################################################################
          ################################################################
          ################################################################
          ################################################################
          ################################################################
          ################################################################
        ###################################################################
     ########################################################################
 ###############################################################################
####################################################################################
 ##################################################################################
  ################################################################################
              #######################################################
               #####################################################
                 #################################################
                  ################################################
                  ################################################
                 ##################################################
                ####################################################
               ############  ##########################  ############
               ##########         #################         #########
              #########              ###########               #######
                 ####                 #########                 ####
                                      #########
                                       #######
                                       #######
                                        #####     </ascii>

    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit is Time.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Uh... a version of myself from the future told me to read this.
        </header>
        <body>
            Well, then future you has excellent taste!

            Seriously, though, it's good you listened.  Always trust future yous and always complete time loops. If you don't, shit gets real. Not even kidding.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Whoa, I have TIME POWERS!?  Freaking SWEET!
        </header>
        <body>
            Excuse me while I just die from laughing at the irony.

            There we go, just had to clear off my superfluous corpse from the computer so I could take over.   The point being: Time is the Shittiest Aspect.  Its all about dealing with a bunch of your own corpses, while knowing that at any moment it might be your turn to join the corpse pile.

            You can't even say that Time makes up for it with Sweet Powers, because you literally die if you use them to do anything but what you're told to. You see a future version of yourself making some coffee, well now you HAVE to make coffee at some point. And even if you were going to anyways, now it fucking sucks because you know you're only doing it because you have to.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Okay, so I stole a frog from that adorable derse agent, and then I pantsed Jack Noir, cheated at poker, and high fived an alien. I THINK I did everything I saw future me do, but the timeline is dooming anyway? This is such flagrant bullshit.
        </header>
        <body>
            Whoa, sounds like you have your stable loops out of control.

            First thing you should do is set up a plan where future versions of yourself shout out some agreed upon code so you know exactly which part in your ridiculous one man ballet they are on.  Even something as simple as "B" can be a big help, because now you know you need to do that after A.

            YES, you are pretty much guaranteed to do it in the right order anyways, but now you no longer have to give yourself a heart attack worrying about it.

            Also, it's entirely possible your timeline doomed for some other reason.  Try to figure out EXACTLY what happened before going back to change anything.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            The timeline doomed and a future me said to check this FAQ before going back to change things.
        </header>
        <body>
            Good for future you and good for current you for listening.

            Listen very carefully:

            DO NOT RUSH TIME TRAVEL.

            You literally have all the time in the world to get this right.  Do NOT go back in time with some half cocked plan that turns out to not even solve the ACTUAL reason shit got doomed.

            Your goal here is to make the smallest number of doomed time clones possible, so make sure you get shit done with only one trip.  You don't want to go back in time to make sure ectobiology happens only to discover that your derpy leader STILL doesn't take care of it even after you save their life.  Shit like that causes "27 doomed time clone" situations as a bunch of yous all come back at once trying to do way-too-little to save the timeline.

            Instead, figure this shit out and have it stick.  Drag your ectobiologist to the equipment if you have to.


        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            The Mind Player is telling me to do something
        </header>
        <body>
            You should probably listen.  Mind seems to be pretty good at knowing places the timeline can go, which means you can focus on doing timey shit instead of caring about decisions.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            The Doom Player is telling me to do something
        </header>
        <body>
            You should probably listen.   Even if they are DIRECTLY leading you to a doomed timeline, it's probably one that's necessary for "everything to go as it already has" or whatever bullshit cryptic phrase they will use.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            WARNING: TIME PLAYERS ONLY PAST THIS POINT

        </header>
        <body>
            CONGRATULATIONS! If you're reading this, you've been saddled with Sburb's worst fucking aspect. That said, this is probably also going to be read by a bunch of you who just ignored the warning at the top, going "Hur de Hur, Time Travel is cool" and plowing straight into a realm that I wouldn't have entered if I'd been given a choice. Fuck you, and fuck your ecto-parents.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why is Time The Worst Aspect?
        </header>
        <body>
            Well, if you've been playing this game for any period longer then say, 5 hours, you may have seen at least one corpse lying around. Statistically, as the time player, that corpse was you. You were the corpse. If you were *really* unlucky, it was the corpse of your friend, your lover, your best buddy, what ever. You probably spent a few hours freaking out about how "OH SHIT I AM GOING TO DIE IN THE FUTURE!" Well, no, you probably won't (Although you might, time travel death paradoxes are just par-for-the-fucking-course-by now), but we'll explain this when we get to doomed timelines later. The main point is that that pile of dead yous/dead friends? That pile does not stop getting taller. You will bury yourself more times then you feel comfortable. Fuck, one time was more then I felt comfortable with. You do get a numbing feeling after the first hundred times though, so I guess it all works out?

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why is a future me screaming at me to not do something?
        </header>
        <body>
            Because you're an unrelenting dick? In seriousness, you have just experienced a [DOOMED TIMELINE]. A [DOOMED TIMELINE] is Skaia's version of a crash, and is one of the main reasons that Time is the worst aspect. Certain events, including unclosed time loops, can set off a [DOOMED TIMELINE]. Once the Timeline has been Doomed, it, and everyone in it, is DOOMED (All caps). They and it will die, disappear, be obliterated, whatever. Shitty. Good for you, you get to travel out of these things! [DOOMED TIMELINES] ignore the normal rules of stable time loops- you CAN go back and fix the problem! Except then you die. Everything from a [DOOMED TIMELINE] stays DOOMED, even if it leaves the timeline. So that future you? Thats a doomed time clone. Do what they say, and make sure to give them a proper burial when the universe decides their Time is up.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How do the time travel?
        </header>
        <body>
            This is the section most likely to be of use to non-time players. Time travel is performed by using the time travel objects. How do you use them? Its fucking obvious, they're just- its- Fuck, look, the objects are just, obvious? If you hold them, you can travel forwards and back in time. How about that.  You don't even need to be a time player.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            How does time fly?
        </header>
        <body>
            Like a banana.

            Wait. shit I think I fucked that up.

            Time flies like an arrow, fruit flies like a banana.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Fuck I Saw Future Me Die?
        </header>
        <body>
            First, confirm that the future you was not a doomed time clone by touching the body. If it is, and you're lucky, you might be able to steal some of his fraymotifs (This game can be really shit at telling you apart from your time clones). Confirmed thats actually Alpha you? Well shit. You have a few options at this point. The obvious one is to do your damned best to make sure you have a source of resurrection on you by the time you die- this may involve you smooching your own corpse. Don't think too hard about it. If you're all out of second chances, then you have my condolences.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How to avoid Future Death?
        </header>
        <body>
            If you have a 100% certain prophecy of your death, don't panic: Sburb has so many ways around death. Consult your Doom player, if you have one, for more advice, or stick around your Life player. If neither of those work, and you are totally sure you have seen your future self die: bullshit it. Go back, forward, sideways, whatever, in time. Do your best to set up a scenario in which that future you *looks* like they died, without actually dying. Use your future knowledge, and yes, you too will be able to trick your past self into seeing your future self die.

        </body>
    </section>

    <section> <header> Help I'm surrounded by dead bodies and they all look like me! </header> <body> Assuming you're a time player, those are all alternate you's who sacrificed themselves to correct your timeline. This is normal, but it does put some strain on spacetime. I recommend you loop your travels rather than try to retcon shit to stop the dead kid pile from growing. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Can i just fetch a frog from a doomed timeline?
        </header>
        <body>
            Answer: No, like no you can't. It's doomed, so you'd have to undoom it and that's completely impossible. Then a perfect frog would have to exist in a doomed timeline to begin with, which would never happen. Finally you'd have to completely flub frog breeding in the alpha timeline anyways to even consider such a stupid plan, which you shouldn't do.
            So in summary, If you are seriously asking this question and not just a what if scenario, yes and you always had to.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What's the most OP way to use time travel?
        </header>
        <body>
            *appears*-shit like this.

            To do-*travels to past*
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Time. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            If you see that your teammates fuck up, fix that. Either employ a stable time loop or be ready to end up doomed.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>