<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>  <ascii>
                                                   #######
                                            ##################
                    ##                    #######
                 ###                   #####
                ###                   ####
               ###                   ###
              ###                   ##
             ###                   ##
            ###                    #
            ###                    #
            ###
            ###                                              #######
            ###                                         ################
            ###                                                      ######
             ###                                                         #####
              ###                                                           ###
               ##                                                             ###
                 #                                                             ###
                   #                                                             ##
                                                                                  ##
                                                                                   #
#
 #
 ##                                                            #
  ##                                                             ##
   ###                                                            ##
    ###                                                            ###
      ###                                                           ###
        #####                                                       ###
           #######         ##                                        ###
              ############                                           ###
                                                                     ###
                                                 #                   ###
                                                ##                   ###
                                               ##                   ###
                                              ###                   ###
                                             ###                   ###
                                           ####                   ###
                                         #####                   ##
                                     ######                    ##
                     ##         ########                     ##
                      ##############

</ascii>

    <section>
        <header>
            Q: What the fuck is this aspect's deal?

        </header>
        <body>
            A: So, this aspect revolves around obfuscation, nonexistence, ignorance, darkness, and secrecy.  So you can get one HELL of a stealth build set up.  Fucking BATMAN levels of hidden predator.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Q: Do I get any cool combat abilities?
        </header>
        <body>
            A: Fuck yes.  Void players get a bonus for attacking from unseen places or surprising enemies.  You auto-crit, which is huge. And combined with your stealth bonuses, you can get SO. MANY. SNEAK. ATTACKS.  A rogue or thief with this aspect would, yes, have their OWN sneak attack feature stack with this, meaning that they could conceivably one-shot even powerful enemies if they get the drop on them. Seers can see weaknesses in enemies, the parts with less material or even more meta-weaknesses, like code issues.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Q:  What are my quests like?

        </header>
        <body>
            A: Quests vary by player, but you can usually assume a few things.  Quests associated with this aspect (it's so damn hard avoiding saying the name) are usually stealth missions.  Sneak past hordes of enemies to get an item.  Successfully hide a macguffin on your person to sneak it into a party without security finding it.  Assassinations, vigilante work, and destruction of evidence are common, as are more mundane hide-and-seek games with consort children.  They're damn perceptive.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Q: What effects does it have on other people In normal interactions? Nobody is talking to me!

        </header>
        <body>
            A: Players interacting with other players tend to notice each other.  Not so with players of this damn aspect-- we get treated as if we don't exist sometimes.  Sometimes it's the other people's fault, because they're unconsciously conditioned to avoid the player.  Other times the whisperings hide you, and higher level void players might even take to embracing them and pulling otherwise easily noticeable pranks mid-conversation.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Q: Did you pants a guy?

        </header>
        <body>
            A: Shut the fuck up.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Q: Things are disappearing when I write them!

        </header>
        <body>
            A: You're noticing the whisperings of Void, the Null. I  tends to eat th ngs that y u write or re ord, e pe ially if yo  inv ke its n me or th  na e of the as ect.

            G d da mit

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Q: My land is bugged and horrible things are showing up...
        </header>
        <body>
            A: [CRITICAL] These are glitches. The influence of the aspect (not naming it, already made that mistake) can cause parts of the game's code to not run or be erased.  This is bad.  Sometimes it will erase parts of the game you don't like, but other times it will erase things you need.  This occurs with Wastes of Void especially.  Get your shit under control and the whisperings will stop glitching shit.

            Hopefully. It could also be the horrorterrors.  In which case, fucking run, assuming that will do any good.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Q: Dungeons are broken!

        </header>
        <body>
            A: This is a known bug.  Void players are not required for any dungeon to open.  You can pass into dungeons that don't require you, and dungeons solely meant for your use will be open all the time after you complete their other requirements, like beating a quest or killing the Denizen, meaning anyone can access them.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            [LIMIT BREAK]
        </header>
        <body>
            This aspect's players have a limit break achieved when they are low on health known as "MAW OF THE ABYSS", which turns you invisible, boosts your attack through the roof, and limits visibility in a half-kilometer radius to around three feet with inky black smoke, which the player can see through clearly.  They also become insubstantial to all physical attacks, and can take the form of a horrible SHADOW MONSTROSITY.  It's fuckin badass.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: The Light Player is always going on about stupid shit and I always tune out halfway through their rants. But when I start listening again they're implying some freaky stuff. What do I do? </header> <body> They're just doing their thing, ignore them. Flashy jerks. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: I'm a Void Player and I'm having trouble doing Void shit. Like I know I can do the cool shit, but I just can't for some reason. </header> <body> Is there a Light Player in your session? Yeah? Well there's your problem! Light Players are jerks, always fussing and meddling and trying to reveal shit that is best left in the Void. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Void Question: What happens when I stare into the void? </header> <body> If you stare into the Void, the Void will stare back. If the Void blinks first, you win! The prize for winning is insanity however. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: What's the void aspect about? </header> <body>
    </body> </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Void. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            [REDACTED]
        </body>
    </section>


</faq>