<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <ascii>

    </ascii>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How bullshit is this bike stunts?
        </header>
        <body>
            Not at all, bro!
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Orbital Transfer
        </header>
        <body>
            Alright, this one is a bit tricky. First, you will need a bike with some sort of rocket propulsion. What you want to do here is ride that sucker as fast as it can go up a ramp, preferably one located on your planet's equator. While airborne, use the rocket to propel you further, and make adjustments to your course by shifting your body weight slightly. You want to get the bike in orbit of your land first, then wait for the perfect spot to boost again, shifting your orbital path so that it intercepts another planets sphere of influence. Best way to do this is to boost while on the side of your planet furthest from the target, and 5-7 minutes of boosting should be enough. When you get reasonably close to the target, shift the bike around and fire the rockets to lower your velocity until you are in a stable orbit(this should take as long as the previous maneuver). The tricky part is choosing a spot to land; I would try to de-orbit yourself when you can see a reasonably safe spot juust over the horizon. Also, bring a parachute. I probably should have mentioned that first.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Help! Everybody in my session is dead and there's no way to get them back!
        </header>
        <body>
            Welp, better go alchemize yourself a bicycle and learn how to do the sweetest bike stunts the Incinisphere has ever seen with the rest of the time you have left.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Is it safer to use my dream self instead of my original self to perform my bike stunts?
        </header>
        <body>
            Of course not! What are you, some kind of poser?
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            BIKE STUNTS
        </header>
        <body>
            what the fuck is that meme
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why do I need a bike, isn’t flying around even cooler?
        </header>
        <body>
            As a professional RealSelf bike stunt-person, I am personally attacked by this question. Seriously though, flying is pretty cool, but with bikes, the fun there is in the danger, it’s in the precise movements, the speed, the spins and flips you pull off as you jump from planet to planet or grind down your moon’s chain, held down by nothing other than the thought that you’re a poser if you’re not doing stunts with your real self.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I see some random dude on a bike doing some hella weird stuff. Care to explain?
        </header>
        <body>Never interrupt someone's sick bike stunts, bro.
        </body>
    </section>


</faq>