<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <ascii>

    </ascii>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How bullshit is everything?
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Help! My friend has just died!
        </header>
        <body>
            Kiss them. In SBURB, necrophilia is a power-up. If that's already happened, try taking them to their QUEST BED or SACRIFICIAL SLAB. It gives them a huge power up. If nothing happens at the bed, they're permadead. Sucks to be you, I guess. It's ok, you start getting blasé about it after a while. It happens to everybody.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Help! My friend is now a dark shadowy beast!
        </header>
        <body>
            It's Horrorterror corruption. They are not from here.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why are you making these?
        </header>
        <body>
            Too much time and too little enemy variety.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Any writing advice?
        </header>
        <body>
            Write anything else other than this. Do not write FAQs, do not pass Go, don't collect 200 boonbucks.
        </body>
    </section>
       <section>
        <header>

        </header>
        <body>

        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Help! My hope player has gone crazy and is screaming about unlimited power!
        </header>
        <body>
            Ok first off, they aren't joking, their power level is literally infinite.
            Do you have a rage player? If yes they can just tank that shit and punch your hope player in the snout until they come back down to reality. If not you've got a bigger problem but basically every aspect but life has a few ways around Unlimited power use them to avoid the power crazed lunatic, hopefully(haha) they will calm down.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Help! People are dying! What do I-
        </header>
        <body>
            DON'T TURN YOUR BACK ON THE BODY! Even if you are 100% sure they are dead, and even if they were alive that they would not be a problem. Never. Turn. Your. Back. On. The. Body.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Can i just skip to the seventh gate?
        </header>
        <body>
            Yeah sure just get a jetpack and PCHOO- no please don't. That gate goes straight to the final boss.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Eww no im not gonna kiss the corpse, no matter what anyone says.
        </header>
        <body>
            K I S S  T H E M
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: My friend is dying help???!!!
        </header>
        <body>
            Kiss the corpse.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question:My coplayer just appeared with a weird, black glow around them, also, I can barely read their text. What is this?
        </header>
        <body>
            That's corruption from the Others. In other news, they will ATTEMPT to crash the game. DO NOT LET THEM. That results in a session failure. If they're the space player, you're pretty much, i dunno, doomed, or something? Heard this from other sources, but some kind of, frog thing is made if the Grimdark space player manages to reverse the progress of the breeding TOO FAR.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question:How do you defend yourself from a Player Killer?
        </header>
        <body>
            Depends on the aspect, and whether they're able to be talked down. IF they can, just attempt to talk em down. If not, or the plan fails, go straight to killing. Get over it, and move on. Grab the pendant, and steal their laptop, and take over being the server player.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question:Okay, I just died, but instead of becoming a dreamself, I'm on a, chessboard land, thing. What is this?
        </header>
        <body>
            Welcome to the battlefield. This is where you go after god-tiering. Now, you should probably find a way back to your land, and or contact your coplayers. Also, the carapaces on the Black Side will attempt to kill you if you’re anywhere along the questline [LONG LIVE THE KING]. Don't let them.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Hey, why do rage players randomly go god tier?
        </header>
        <body>
            If magic is all we've ever known
            Then it's easy to miss what really goes on
            But I've seen miracles in every way
            And I see miracles everyday
            Oceans spanning beyond my sight
            And a million stars way above em at night
            We don't have to be high to look in the sky
            And know that's a miracle opened wide
            Look at the mountains, trees, the seven seas
            And everything chilling underwater, please
            Hot lava, snow, rain and fog
            Long neck giraffes, and pet cats and dogs
            And I've seen eighty-five thousand people
            All in one room, together as equals
            Pure magic is the birth of my kids
            I've seen shit that'll shock your eyelids
            The sun and the moon, and even Mars
            The Milky Way and fucking shooting stars
            UFOs, a river flows
            Plant a little seed and nature grows
            Niagara falls and the pyramids
            Everything you believed in as kids
            Fucking rainbows after it rains
            There's enough miracles here to blow your brains
            I fed a fish to a pelican at Frisco bay
            It tried to eat my cell phone, he ran away
            And music is magic, pure and clean
            You can feel it and hear it but it can't be seen

            Music is all magic
            (Are you a firm believer in miracles)
            You can't even hold it
            (Do you notice and recognize miracles)
            It's just there in the air
            (Are you a firm believer in miracles)
            theres more
            Pure motherfucking magic
            Right?
            This shit'll blow your fucking mind
            (Do you notice and recognize miracles)

            Music is a lot like love, it's all a feeling
            And it fills the room, from the floor to the ceiling
            I see miracles all around me
            Stop and look around, it's all astounding
            Water, fire, air and dirt
            Fucking magnets, how do they work?
            And I don't wanna talk to a scientist
            Y'all motherfuckers lying, and getting me pissed
            Solar eclipse, and vicious weather
            Fifteen thousand Juggalos together
            And I love my mom for giving me this
            Time on this planet, taking nothing for granted
            I seen a caterpillar turn into a butterfly
            Miracles ain't nothing to lie
            Shaggy's little boys look just like Shaggy
            And my little boy looks just like daddy
            Miracles each and every where you look
            And nobody has to stay where they put
            This world is yours for you to explore
            There's nothing but miracles beyond your door
            The Dark Carnival is your invitation
            To witness them without explanation
            Take a look at this fine creation
            And enjoy it better with appreciation
            Crows, ghosts, the midnight coast
            The wonders of the world, mysteries the most
            Just open your mind, and it ain't no way
            To ignore the miracles of every day

            (Are you a firm believer in miracles)
            Magic everywhere in this bitch
            (Do you notice and recognize miracles)
            It's all around you, you don't even know it
            (Are you a firm believer in miracles)
            Magic everywhere in this bitch
            Shit's crazy
            (Do you notice and recognize miracles,
            So many miracles, the magic miracles)

            Are you a firm believer in miracles
            Do you have time for the miracles
            Do you notice and recognize miracles
            So many miracles, the magic miracles
            Are you a firm believer in miracles
            Do you have time for the miracles
            Do you notice and recognize miracles
            So many miracles, the magic miracles
            Are you a firm believer in miracles
            Do you have time for the miracles
            Do you notice and recognize miracles
            So many miracles, the magic miracles
            Are you a firm believer in miracles
            Do you have time for the miracles
            Do you notice and recognize miracles
            So many miracles, the magic miracles        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I heard [A thing] about [ASPECT], why is the witch ignoring it.
        </header>
        <body>
            Because witches are weird man, haven't you ever read a fairy tale?
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why did the witch just did the most draw dropping shit i have ever seen and completely changed the session, why isn't she doing that on a regular basis?
        </header>
        <body>
            Ever seen in fairy tales how witches rewrite the story and all it's rules then kinda are irrelevant? It's like that.
            Mechanically witches have a second hidden pluck bar which is HUGE like 1000x what it should, but they can only tap it when it's like 2-300+x their normal bar and it only fills up from overflow of their normal bar.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Hey, where is the Void pla- OHGOD
        </header>
        <body>
            Did they just appear right behind you? Thought so. Void has a shit ton of stealth powers.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why do I hear angry and loud voices in my head?
        </header>
        <body>
            Just Exiles. You probably gave them a bad impression. Or the Caps-Lock is on. Alternatively, horrerterrors, in which case you should go hug someone.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why is the rage player already God-Tier? I've only just entered the game.
        </header>
        <body>
            Giggle-snort.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: The ghost puppet thing won't shut up! How do I make it stop!
        </header>
        <body>
            You don't. So unless you can get the Time player to jump in the Kernal for you, you're stuck with that horrible abomination.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: why do i keep dying to a giant snake?
        </header>
        <body>
            Thats called a denizen,and maybe you should abscond befere you have a Unlucky Br8k
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: It keeps happening!
        </header>
        <body>
            I warned you about the stairs bro!
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: My friend just went crazy! I think they want to kill me! Oh God Oh God Oh God Oh-
        </header>
        <body>
            Calm down. There are two ways to deal with this, either calm their asses down or put their asses down. If the second is the only option, I’m sorry for your loss.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What's this Swirly Lollipop?
        </header>
        <body>
            Put it down. Just put it down. Walk away and never look back.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: There are things... in the sky, or not the sky? Whatever it there are things, whispering things above, err below? Things around Derse, just what are they?
        </header>
        <body>
            Don't worry about it.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: But-
        </header>
        <body>
            No, just no. They less you know the better.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What are you doing?
        </header>
        <body>
            Making chocolate pudding.
        </body>
        <header>
            Question: Why on earth are you making chocolate pudding at 4 in the morning?
        </header>
        <body>
            Because I've lost control of my life.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Are you losing control over your life?
        </header>
        <body>
            Yes.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            How do I grind up that wicked verballistamina?
        </header>
        <body>
            You gotta get absolutely NOIDED at the verbullshitstick crazytoriumhouse my dude.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Someone made a robot and the robot went murdermode! What do I do?!
        </header>
        <body>
            What kind of man builds a machine to kill a kid? No, he did not use his hands; like a smart man, he used a tool...
            But just the same! Can you question who's to blame?
            My advice is to put it down immediately!
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Can I kick it?
        </header>
        <body>
            Yes you can!
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What is the purple frog.
        </header>
        <body>
            The frog is the lotus of your session, it symbolizes your creation. The purple lotus represents openness to enlightenment, by seeking the purple frog you are showing the enlightenment offered by the horror terrors. It is will try to kill you.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why is the purple frog trying to kill me?!
        </header>
        <body>
            It merely seeks to liberate you from your physical form that you may further your enlightenement in dream bubbles, unlike other dead you shall continue to grow.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How do you get the Purple frog?
        </header>
        <body>
            -100% Frog breeding.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I have done it! I have alchemized a weapon to kill gods!
        </header>
        <body>
            No you haven't. In five minutes you'll complete a quest and get some loot then make something even better, rinse and repeat. Do you even RPG?
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I just killed this giant ogre thing by myself! I feel like I could do anything!
        </header>
        <body>
            Good for you. But by the end of the day you'll be taking out Ogres easier than you do Imps now. Do you even RPG?
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: I was freaking out but then I took some time to calm down and go back the playing the game. But I started freaking out again! </header> <body> Catch-22: Sburb edition. </body> </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How do I win the game?
        </header>
        <body>
            Don't play.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: What does going "God Tier" mean? Is it a kind of power boost? </header> <body> No. Just, no. God-Tiering is not a power boost, it is a complete transformation, a metamorphosis of mind, body and soul. It is not to be taken lightly. It is like a baptism of fire and fury, your soul laid bare to the full power of your Aspect. And if you think you understand your Aspect, that you got it "under control" you can't be more wrong. If you really want to do it, and if you find out how to do it, because you will only learn of it if you are meant to. Then you will lay down a child with the makings of a Hero and rise a hero with the makings of a God. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> What is this little ball thing that keeps following me around? (Sorry if this is obvious, I just started...) </header> <body> That "little ball thing" is your Kernelsprite. You can prototype it by depositing any object into it. If you do so, when you enter the game, it will become your sprite, and cryptically "help you." It is recommended you prototype something sentient [or something that was sentient, it can resurrect things!] to be your guide. However, beware prototyping something too powerful, as all enemies you will ever face will gain the powers and abilities of the prototyped object. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: Why do I have a rounded cube in my hands? </header> <body> Thats a perfectly generic object </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: What the fuck is this thing on my hands? </header> <body> That's a perfectly unique object. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> I just woke up on Derse, and I can swear I can hear whispering just behind me, but whenever I turn around there's no one there. </header> <body> What you're hearing are the Horrorterrors that rule over the domain beyond the Furthest Ring. They're mostly harmless, just ignore them and you'll be fine. They do know a lot about SBURB, but they always want something from you. I consider this FAQ a better source of info to be honest. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Help I'm being swarmed by weird lizard things and thNAK NAK NAK NAK WHAT IS THIS THING NAK NAK THIS THING IS ASKING ME TO SEND NAK NAK NAK SEND? </header> <body> Oh you poor dude. I hope you get your computing device back. If you do, those are your consorts. They are the dumb as fuck NPCs you have to do stuff for/to/with to complete your personal quest. They also sell some items, so be sure to check them out once you've saved up enough Boonbucks. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> What's happening? The Battlefield is being pelted by meteors! </header> <body> That's the Reckoning, the final stage of the game, so make sure someone has done the ectobiology, and someone has bred the Tadpole, then head to the Battlefield for the final boss fight, you can't miss them. Good luck! </body> </section>
    <section> <header> So what's all this about a Black Queen? </header> <body> So you know how in some games, there are secret bosses? Stupid amounts of power, a ton of abilities, probably wipes out your party, maybe even more than once? It's exactly bit like that, but it isnt very optional and this not so secret boss has a chance of being made into not a boss which might be the most preferable situtation for you. Sometimes you might be able to get her to take off the ring, usually by prototyping some kind of amphibian, or maybe even get shenanigans or an uprising to kill her or at least un-ring her, if not you will have to fight her. The Black Queen has a lot of things you should watch out for: she's got all your prototypes stored up in her thanks to the ring, giving her their power and abilities, and she's got the Red Miles, also thanks to the ring. You can't escape the Miles. You can try but you just can't. Good Luck. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Help! Meteors are falling everywhere! How do I get in this game already! </header> <body> First off, dying from a meteor is probably better than being in this game, but if you really want to, get your server player to place down the free buildings, the Cruxtruder, Punch Designex, Totem lathe, and Alchemiter, along with the pre-punched card. With all of those placed down, you need to open up the Cruxtruder, which requires a lot of force, so get your server player to drop something heavy on it, that usually works. A long cylinder should come out, along with some glowy flashy sphere and a countdown on the Cruxtruder.The countdown is how long you have to do all these random things until your death by fiery meteor, that cylinder is called a Cruxite Dowel, and the flashy thing is the Kernelsprite. Make sure you toss something into that thing before you enter the session, preferably NOT something extremely powerful, or else your session is screwed before you even start. I know this is really tedious, but next, take that Dowel and the Pre-Punched card and stick them into the Totem Lathe. That should cut the dowel into a new shape, the Cruxite Totem, which you can put into the Alchemiter to get some sort of Cruxite Artifact, which is different for each person. Using or doing whatever the Artifact wants you to do will put you into the session. Good luck. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: What does the Jumper block do? </header> <body> The jumper block can connect to the alchemiter to allow for some level of customization. While this can be easily exploited to make alchemy MUCH more convenient, you should be careful with what you use. One player in my session tried to use it in conjunction with a glass of water, and pretty much turned the entire device into water. They were left with a very wet house, no way to do alchemy, and lost some perfectly good capchalogue cards. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I've just installed SBURB, but its not doing anything.
        </header>
        <body>
            SBURB isn't a game you can play alone*. Once installed, you can choose to either play as a Server or a Client player. It doesn't matter which you choose. You'll eventually play both, whether you like it or not.

            *typically. Some people claim that it's been done before. Probably just another bogus rumor, though. I wouldn't try it.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What is the difference between a Server and a Client player?
        </header>
        <body>
            It's actually pretty self explanitory. A Server player Hosts a Client Player in a session. The Client player connects to a Server Player. What ISN'T self explanitory is the duties of both players; A Server Player is required to add constructions and modify the Client Player's home in order to prepare them for entry into their Session. Meanwhile, it's the Client Player's duty to actually enter.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Alright, I'm a Server Player. Now what?
        </header>
        <body>
            Once your Client connects, you should be able to see them on your screen along with menus for adding constructions. There's a few objects you'll want to add as soon as possible. The Cruxtruder, The Alchemiter, the Totem Lathe, the Punch Designix and the Pre-Punched Card are the most important. They should be free to build, but the more Clients and Servers you have connected to your session, the more objects and add-ons will be available. For now, just focus on placing the objects listed above and get ready for the game to begin.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            My player's room is too small! I can't put all this stuff in here!
        </header>
        <body>
            Remember when I said you can modify the player's home? You can do that. From the Menus, you should be able to select the option to create more rooms. Just click and drag where you want to expand and viola. More floorspace! The walls and ceilings will adjust to fit, so don't worry about that. You can also add and remove doors, windows, stairs, and walkways! Pesky Furniture in the way? Click and drag it to another room! Toss it on the roof, who cares? I'm sure that priceless family portrait would look great hanging on the front door.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I've placed the Cruxtruder, but it's not doing anything? What's the point of this big stupid thing!
        </header>
        <body>
            Did you also place the Alchemiter, Totem Lathe, Punch Designix, and the Pre-Punched Card? If no, DON'T TOUCH THAT YET. If yes, then strap in. Shit is about to get real! The Cruxtruder can be opened by applying significant force to the cap on the top of that little pipe jutting up from the center of the machine. Once you pop the lid on that soda-can, a couple things will fly free: The Cruxite Dowel and the Kernel Sprite*. Have your player take that Dowel and bring it to the Totem Lathe.

            *more on that later
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            The Totem Lathe looks like something I saw on TV...
        </header>
        <body>
            It's a Lathe. It carves Totems. In SBURB, Totems act like 3D Barcodes for the Alchemiter to create objects with. There should be a Punch Card Slot on the side of the machine. Instruct your player to place the Dowel on the Lathe and insert the Pre Punched Card into the slot. The Lathe will carve the Dowel for you to use on the Alchemiter. Oh, and seriously insist on your player hurrying up. You have more important things to worry about than carving tons of totems right now.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            The Alchemiter looks neat. How do I use it?
        </header>
        <body>
            The Alchemiter is the machine that will allow you to create items and objects to be used in SBURB! There should be a pedestal with a weird geometrical design on it. If you place any carved Dowels on that pedestal, the Alchemiter will scan it and create the object designated by the Dowel's shape. Each Dowel is unique, based on the Punch Card used to make it. Tell your player to put the Dowel you made using the Pre Punched Card on it and get ready to enter.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Hey is it me, or is my player sweating a lot? Did it get hotter? Why am I hearing explosion? WAS THAT A METEOR???
        </header>
        <body>
            Oh right. The Meteors. I forgot to mention the Meteors.Yeah sorry for dropping the ball on that one. Meteors, dude. Remember when you opened the Cruxtruder? There should be a timer on it that's counting down. That's pretty much how long you have until your player's smashed by a big rock from the sky. That's why shit was getting real. So stop wasting time.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            That glowing orb thing keeps bothering my player. Is it Hostile?
        </header>
        <body>
            No no. Well... I don't know, maybe? That's the Kernelsprite. If it's bothering your player, it means it wants to be Prototyped. Toss something in and it should transform and calm down a little. You can only prototype a sprite twice, so make it count. Some people like to toss in meaningful things, and others just toss in whatever. It really doesn't matter, just so long as you actually do it. You MUST prototype the Kernel at least ONCE before you enter though, or else the game is going to go bonkers. You can do it twice before entry too, but I hear it makes the game harder...
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            The Alchemiter created something weird when my player put the Totem Dowel on it.
        </header>
        <body>
            That is the player's Totem. If you've prototyped your Kernelsprite at least once, use it. USE IT RIGHT NOW!!!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Wait, where did my player go?
        </header>
        <body>
            Good job! Your player just enterred the Medium. They should be on their Land now. Don't get comfortable though. Your job isn't over just yet.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section> <header> Question: Everything has gone horribly wrong and all my friends are dying. Help! </header> <body> That's not a question, but ok. This is probably because you are in a doomed timeline. If you aren't the time player, I advise making peace with your god. You're screwed by skaia. If you are the time player, this is probably all your fault. But don't give up hope! It's also your job to fix it. Just travel back in time and try and make sure the players don't screw up then. Of course, this might be the way the timeline is supposed to go, in which case traveling back in time will only screw stuff up worse. Gee golly time sure is the shittiest aspect. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            OH NO: I really, really, really don't feel like playing this game anymore.
        </header>
        <body>
            Unfortunately for you, there are only two ways out of this.

            1: Win.
            2: Die.

            I'm not sure if you've tried to take the second way out, but it doesn't work. Not as long as you want it. So you have to play, because it's the only thing you can do, and if you don't, then the game has plenty worse ways to make you suffer other than death.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            OH NO: Why should I keep playing this game? I'm struggling to find a meaning.
        </header>
        <body>
            Don't want to spoil it for you, but if all goes as planned, this game's ending will be the best of any game you've ever played. Except, well, it's not really a game. What you need to know is that if you decide to give up now, you will just let yourself down, you will let everyone else down. The very nature of the game requires that all players cooperate toward achieving a singular goal or else chaos ensues. By giving up, you are essentially giving the biggest middle finger possible to everyone else in the game.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            OH NO: Why should I care about playing if all my friends are dead?
        </header>
        <body>
            Frankly, depending on how far you got before this happened, you don't have much a chance at winning the game. One option is that you're in a doomed timeline, and in that case, there isn't much you can do. I've heard some people try talking to their Denizen, if it's still alive, and it can rarely provide you with an option that will help out some other instance of you in another frame of existence.

            However, in the event that you're not in a doomed timeline... well, sucks to be you, eh? Better find something to occupy your time, because you're likely to have a lot of it. It's not forever, oh no, trust me, but you're going to need to find something to keep your mind busy, fast.

            Most people just do bike stunts.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            OH NO: I'm the last living player and am getting kind of bored of bike stunts. What now?
        </header>
        <body>
            First of all, no one can ever get bored of bike stunts. Ever. That's just a thing that doesn't happen.

            In the event that you have managed to get bored of bike stunts, congratulations. You're a statistical anomaly. Now, I hate to break it to you, but yeah, you don't have forever. Eventually an event called the Reckoning will occur, and all those meteors floating in Derse's orbit will start flying toward Skaia. Since you're the last one alive, it's pointless for me to tell you why this is happening and what it means.

            What is important, however, is that by the Reckoning's end, Skaia is destroyed, including the Battlefield. If you had maybe a 0.0001% chance of victory before, it's 0% now. You cannot win without Skaia. The Army of Darkness has succeeded in their mission, however suicidal it may have been.

            However, basically unknown to anyone at all (trust me, you won't find much about this any of Prospit, Derse, or your land's libraries) is that at the center of the Battlefield, far beneath its chessboard surface, there is a bomb. It varies in size from session to session and doesn't seem to correlate to any known variables. In some sessions it can fit in the palm of your hands, in others it's the size of a skyscraper. Regardless of size, this bomb is powerful enough to completely obliterate your session. It will go off as soon as the game detects that the Reckoning is complete.

            In short, you're done for. No way around that.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            OH NO: I've some how come into possession into a weird ying-yang looking thing that was found in the center of the Battlefield. What do I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Well, that ying-yang looking thing is the most lethal bomb known to man, consort, and carapace. Don't try using it, or alchemizing it into anything, because it never ends well. This bomb is designed to completely obliterate your session and everyone in it should things ever go awry. So yeah. You're better off just leaving that thing where you found it, because you wouldn't want to set it off accidentally, would you?

            Now, I have heard rumors of ways to dispose of this bomb, but no matter how hard you try, this thing will inevitably detonate. That doesn't mean it has to detonate inside your session, however. I once heard a story about a group of players who took the bomb, put it on a Skaian Battleship, then flung that thing Out of Bounds. I'm not sure what happened after that, but I assume that the bomb must have exploded somewhere in deep space, or some unlucky kids got a face full of session-shattering-kaboom. Either way, the group that did the disposing never had to worry about the bomb ever again.

            Oh yeah, and that group may have been mine (but in a doomed timeline), and that story may have been on the wall in one of the ruins on my Land. Prophecies, eh? Gotta love 'em.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            OH NO: I just saw a painting of a bunch of dead kids somewhere on my land! What does this mean?
        </header>
        <body>
            Well, clearly it means that a bunch of kids are going to die in your session. Them's the breaks. However, a lot of the time these paintings, engravings, or statues, however they may appear, are intentionally vague. Sure, a bunch of kids are going to die in your session, but maybe they're not your players. Maybe some other players show up, and all get slaughtered by whatever it is that lives beyond the session's boundaries just minutes before crossing it.

            So please, do remember to analyze your prophecies carefully. Or, you could just ask a Seer, or a Hero of Doom.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> OH NO: Oh my god, they're dead. They can come back, right? Right? Oh my god, please tell me that they can come back! </header> <body> If you haven't kissed them yet, do it now. If you die in the game, you die in real life. </body> </section> <section> <header> OH NO: I just kissed my dead friend and they're like, flying or something now. What happened? </header> <body> Standard kiss revival procedure. In layman's terms, their dreamself has merged with their real self. The only real difference this makes is that they can fly now, and also one other thing, but I'm not quite going to spoil that for you. Everybody gets one. </body> </section> <section> <header> OH NO: I just kissed my dead friend and nothing happened! What's this all about? </header> <body> Hate to break it to you, but there's a 97% chance that you're friend is perma-dead. Unfortunately there's very little you can do about that now, unless you somehow have acquired the power to bring back the dead. Ask a life player. </body> </section> <section> <header> OH NO: So... my friend is dead. Forever. They're not coming back. Why should I continue? </header> <body> Take a deep breath. Count to 10. Whisper this to yourself.
    "The game must go on."
    SBURB stops for no one. It will not stop for the deaths of your players, and it will not stop to let you grieve about it. Refusing to play is a one-way ticket to Deathville, population: you. It sounds wrong, but the best thing to do is to forget about your friend and keep playing the game.
    There will be plenty of time to grieve when it's over. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> QUESTION:Help, I accidentally prototyped a big strong thing, and now Jack Noir has the ring! Help! </header> <body> Welp, you're fucked. Go for a scratch, or just escape into the veil. There is one thing, however. If a Witch of Space prototyped the thing in the first place, Jack Noir will NOT attack them. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I've heard a few things about getting consort companions. How would I go about doing that?
        </header>
        <body>
            That's a great question. As a Hero of Blood, your powers will be put to their best use when in charge of a group. Whether this group be consorts, players, hired underlings, or carapacians, you're the best. If you've sufficiently advanced along your quest, most consorts will recognize you as being the hero of the land. Some may ask for you to complete a quest first, but none of these quests are too hard. The problem is that not all consorts who are easy to find are the best for your party. Sure, you could lead a party of a thousand weak consorts, but as a group gets larger it also becomes harder to manage. You'll want to look for rare consorts with special titles. Those guys can dish out insane amounts of damage that is only further multiplied by your powers.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What is the point of the game?
        </header>
        <body>
            Answer: Well, that's rather simple actually. The po nt o th ga   i  t si











            Damn void players.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Why are all my FAQ's fucked up?
        </header>
        <body>
            People aren't using the proper formatting when submitting them >:L
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            FAQ # 572:  These weird little animal dudes keep asking me to do stupid shit. They want me to deliver their letters, watch their kids, do their shopping, yell at their neighbors for them... Why should I do any of this?
        </header>
        <body>
            Welcome to SBURB, the shitty Live Action Role-Playing Game. Those little guys are usually referred to as your consorts, and grinding rep with them is going to be a big part of the early game. Take whatever quests they give you, and eventually they will unlock some sweet fraymotifs, weapons, and other phat lewt. They're basically NPCs, but they're not totally bound to a script. If you're a big enough asshole, they WILL turn on you.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            FAQ # 6969: HOW BULLSHIT IS BULLSHIT
        </header>
        <body>
            YES
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>

        <header> Help! a God tiered Witch of space in my session took a acrobatic leap into a pile of crazy and is killing everyone! What do I do?!?! </header>

        <body> Run! NOW! Space players are powerful but usually not very mobile. And hope they don't have any beef with you in particular. </body>

    </section>

    <section>
        <header> Question: How come you are the authority here, anyways?</header>
        <body> Because I said so. </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: My denizen is just a title what do i do?!?!
        </header>
        <body>
            Answer: [Critical Threat] You got one of the special denizens, these will all give you weird and/or extreme choices, they also WILL basically wreck your shit if you don't take the choice. So take the damn choice. However some of them can give some pretty awesome stuff with their choices if you can get past the grade S giggle snort hidey talk they bring.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Wait, so by using the Alchemiter, I can combine ANYTHING!?
        </header>
        <body>
            Of course! Well, provided you can afford it, of course. Lots of combat and utility items you can create with the alchemiter can be expensive, especially the overpowered stuff. So if you wanna get that death ray, you gotta save up big time.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Are purple flames that spread darkness a normal Vo-- power? Because our Witch of V__d is really freaking me out.
        </header>
        <body>
            No, that is NOT normal. I've never heard of anything like that before, but you should probably keep a close eye on them, if you can. Voii|||iidD players can be hard to find if they don't want to be found.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section> <header> Question: What are these lizard guys and why won't they leave me alone? </header> <body> Unless you prototyped something lizardlike, those are probably your consorts.  Consorts are the npcs of sburb, so expect to spend a lot of time around them.  Consorts give quests to help them out in some way and can hand out lore in piecemeal chunks.  Depending on your land you may even find consorts strong enough to fight beside you, or armies of them to lead.</body> </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Q: My Denizen gave me an impossible quest. Not just really hard, I mean literally impossible. And if I fail, it's going to kill me. It's a giant fucking monster, I don't care how many stupid video-game weapons I have, I can't fight it! What the hell am I supposed to do?
            --kindredDirector
        </header>
        <body>
            You better think harder about that quest, boyo. If a Denizen gives you a Quest, or a Choice (note the capital letters there) there is  a l w a y s  a way to complete it. The Denizens' purpose is to challenge you and make you stronger.

            Fuck it up and they will totally kill you, tho.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Q: Some asshole showed up in a red suit with some clearly fake gold on. He's not doing much, but he won't stop singing some inane gibberish. Am I getting raided or is this somehow an actual fucking mechanic?
        </header>
        <body>
            Congrats, you've fucked up hard enough to summon a savior. These are session-displaced players, possibly since the game even came into genesis, who just kinda hang out. They're sent out by the game when things go south enough to loop back into winnable, at which point, they sing, slaughter and skedaddle. Just let them do their thing and try not to think about it too much.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What's the recommended amount of dedicated ram needed to run SBURB?
        </header>
        <body>
            From what information I've gathered, it literally does not matter. The moment you insert the disk into your computer, the game optimizes itself for peak performance. Yes, this means you can run SBURB on any computer with a mouse, keyboard, and monitor.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Is SBURB compatible with controllers?
        </header>
        <body>
            They seem to work for placing objects and building homes just fine, providing comfort at the cost of precision. It even seems like motion sensing remotes work, but personally I'd recommend against using them due to how unresponsive they are at times.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: All my friends are telling me that I needed to insert my SBURB disks into my computer, but I inserted them into my gaming console instead! Did I mess up already?
        </header>
        <body>
            LOL, no. Hope you like 30 FPS!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Everyone's telling me that I can fly now that I've died, what are they talking about?
        </header>
        <body>
            If you've died in-game, no matter which way you've come back, your new form has the ability to fly. Just try it!
        </body>
    </section>
    <header>
        Some random weirdos just showed up in our session! They claim to be players from another session! What the actual fuck!?
    </header>
    <body>
        Ooh, combo session! You're gonna have a lot of fun!
    </body>
    <section><header>
        Can I have a really cool item code?
    </header>
        <body>
            No.
        </body></section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I'm in a combo session!
        </header>
        <body>
            So, you're in a combo session! That means that there were some people playing Sburb just like you, and they fucked up. Spoiler! The point of the game is to create a universe and the previous players created yours, but they did it wrong. So to try and escape their horrible mistakes they came to your session to both help you and help themselves.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Players from another session are killing my friends! I thought this game was about teamwork!
        </header>
        <body>
            They'll do that. They've been in this game for far longer than you have, especially if you're somewhere down the chain of a triple or greater combo session. This game tends to break people, and the longer you spend in it the more you'll break. Never think you're at rock bottom, there's always somewhere even deeper and shittier.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            My friend died, and now he's alive again? But he's wearing really stupid pajamas. What the hell is going on?
        </header>
        <body>It's important, but please make fun of them. It's hilarious.
        </body>
    </section>

</faq>