<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How bullshit is everything?
        </header>
        <body>
           Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Help! My friend has just died!
        </header>
        <body>
            Kiss them. In SBURB, necrophilia is a power-up. If that's already happened, try taking them to their QUEST BED or SACRIFICIAL SLAB. It gives them a huge power up. If nothing happens at the bed, they're permadead. Sucks to be you, I guess. It's ok, you start getting blasé about it after a while. It happens to everybody.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Help! My friend is now a dark shadowy beast!
        </header>
        <body>
            It's Horrorterror corruption. They are not from here.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why are you making these?
        </header>
        <body>
            Too much time and too little enemy variety.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Any writing advice?
        </header>
        <body>
            Write anything else other than this. Do not write FAQs, do not pass Go, don't collect 200 boonbucks.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Tricksters
        </header>
        <body>
            So, I'm going to preface this by saying that the fact that you need to read this faq means a decent chance that you're screwed. I'm sorry, it's just a fact of life. This guide will help you to either maximize what little time you have left, or learn about preventing tricksters from attacking.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            So what is a trickster?
        </header>
        <body>
            Tricksters are probably the single most chaotic and malevolent entity that sburb can possibly produce. Seriously. A trickster can tank the black king, the black queen, hell, it could probably kill a debug NPC if it felt like it.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why wouldn't I want to be a Trickster, then?
        </header>
        <body>
            Imagine if you will looking out in horror as your skin turns to sugar and your brains into candy, as even as you speak your words become saccharine and your thoughts go mad, and you want it off but you can't resist it. If the answer to any of these questions was a yes, then get some help. If you are a trickster, you are not you. Tricksters care only about candy, "fun", and reproduction. If you manage to become one, any goals or relationships you had before you did are screwed.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            How do you become one?
        </header>
        <body>
            This is one that I really, really hesitate to answer. For the sake of avoidance, however, I will. In order to become a trickster, you need something with a certain intrinsic quality. We don't really know what it is, or what this quality is, only that it exists. My guess is that it's always candy, but I may be wrong. Ours was a massive jawbreaker. It had this sort of red and green swirl pattern, and the temptation of eating it was irresistible. You just have to eat it, or do whatever your body instinctively does when it touches the item. Other than that, just let yourself get kissed, kicked in the genitals, or something else weird by the trickster(s).

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What can a trickster do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Tricksters can do essentially anything. They can fly, create life, alchemize without grist, create grist, are basically invulnerable, have pretty much infinite strength and endurance, massive speed, know exactly what to say to hurt you, and are completely insane. They can do other stuff if they feel like it. One guy got trapped in a sort of infinite loop within a santa doll. He eventually went trickster, and the rest is history.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            How do you stop them?
        </header>
        <body>
            There are pretty much two ways to stop a trickster from attacking you. Death doesn't work, they'll just resurrect you, and god tiers can only hold them off for so long. No, the only ways to stop them are with a) a Zillyweapon, or b) outside interference. The first can be very rarely found through temporal shenanigans or normal quests, or through usage of the grist that tricksters secrete(?) called Zillium. Zillium can make Zillyweapons and some other weird stuff, which is all insanely strong. The weapons won't corrupt you, but too much zillium can, and it can be used to make a trickster item. Be on your toes if you ever find any. The outside interference part I've only heard about. Supposedly, some sort of outside force can end trickster corruption for good through time travel (not loops) or cleansing or something. Don't bet on that happening, though.


        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Recognizing a trickster
        </header>
        <body>
            Tricksters have bright, neon hair and clothes, are covered in candy, weird skin (it disobeys the laws of reality somehow), and talk in a voice that can't be replicated. They will talk in a sugary sweet, sexually perverse, creepy as hell way. If you can see it, it can probably see you. Say your prayers.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            In conclusion
        </header>
        <body>
            Tricksters are undoubtedly a huge threat. Luckily, they're very rare and don't focus at all on finishing the game. If either of those were to be false, we'd be screwed. If you suspect someone of being a trickster, stay away, tell your friends to stay away, as well as any pets you may have. Try to get a Zillyweapon. Other than that, just pray that you don't get found.

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>

        </header>
        <body>

        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Help! My hope player has gone crazy and is screaming about unlimited power!
        </header>
        <body>
            Ok first off, they aren't joking, their power level is literally infinite.
            Do you have a rage player? If yes they can just tank that shit and punch your hope player in the snout until they come back down to reality. If not you've got a bigger problem but basically every aspect but life has a few ways around Unlimited power use them to avoid the power crazed lunatic, hopefully(haha) they will calm down.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Help! People are dying! What do I-
        </header>
        <body>
            DON'T TURN YOUR BACK ON THE BODY! Even if you are 100% sure they are dead, and even if they were alive that they would not be a problem. Never. Turn. Your. Back. On. The. Body.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Can i just skip to the seventh gate?
        </header>
        <body>
            Yeah sure just get a jetpack and PCHOO- no pls don't. i beg.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Eww no im not gonna kiss the-
        </header>
        <body>
            K I S S  T H E M
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: My friend is dying help???!!!
        </header>
        <body>
            Kiss them
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question:My coplayer just appeared with a weird, black glow around them, also, I can barely read their text. What is this?
        </header>
        <body>
            That's corruption from the Others. In other news, they will ATTEMPT to crash the game. DO NOT LET THEM. That results in a session failure. If they're the space player, you're pretty much, i dunno, doomed, or something? Heard this from other sources, but some kind of, frog thing is made if the Grimdark space player manages to reverse the progress of the breeding TOO FAR.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question:How do you defend yourself from a Player Killer?
        </header>
        <body>
            Depends on the aspect, and whether they're able to be talked down. IF they can, just attempt to talk em down. If not, or the plan fails, go straight to killing. Get over it, and move on. Grab the pendant, and steal their laptop, and take over being the server player.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question:Okay, I just died, but instead of well, becoming a dreamself, I'm on a, chessboard land, thing. What is this?
        </header>
        <body>
            Welcome to the battlefield. This is where you go after god-tiering. Now, you should probably find a way back to your land, and or contact your coplayers. Also, the carapaces on the Black Side will attempt to kill you. Don't let them.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Hey, why do rage players randomly go god tier?
        </header>
        <body>
            If magic is all we've ever known
            Then it's easy to miss what really goes on
            But I've seen miracles in every way
            And I see miracles everyday
            Oceans spanning beyond my sight
            And a million stars way above em at night
            We don't have to be high to look in the sky
            And know that's a miracle opened wide
            Look at the mountains, trees, the seven seas
            And everything chilling underwater, please
            Hot lava, snow, rain and fog
            Long neck giraffes, and pet cats and dogs
            And I've seen eighty-five thousand people
            All in one room, together as equals
            Pure magic is the birth of my kids
            I've seen shit that'll shock your eyelids
            The sun and the moon, and even Mars
            The Milky Way and fucking shooting stars
            UFOs, a river flows
            Plant a little seed and nature grows
            Niagara falls and the pyramids
            Everything you believed in as kids
            Fucking rainbows after it rains
            There's enough miracles here to blow your brains
            I fed a fish to a pelican at Frisco bay
            It tried to eat my cell phone, he ran away
            And music is magic, pure and clean
            You can feel it and hear it but it can't be seen

            Music is all magic
            (Are you a firm believer in miracles)
            You can't even hold it
            (Do you notice and recognize miracles)
            It's just there in the air
            (Are you a firm believer in miracles)
            theres more
            Pure motherfucking magic
            Right?
            This shit'll blow your fucking mind
            (Do you notice and recognize miracles)

            Music is a lot like love, it's all a feeling
            And it fills the room, from the floor to the ceiling
            I see miracles all around me
            Stop and look around, it's all astounding
            Water, fire, air and dirt
            Fucking magnets, how do they work?
            And I don't wanna talk to a scientist
            Y'all motherfuckers lying, and getting me pissed
            Solar eclipse, and vicious weather
            Fifteen thousand Juggalos together
            And I love my mom for giving me this
            Time on this planet, taking nothing for granted(edited)
            I seen a caterpillar turn into a butterfly
            Miracles ain't nothing to lie
            Shaggy's little boys look just like Shaggy
            And my little boy looks just like daddy
            Miracles each and every where you look
            And nobody has to stay where they put
            This world is yours for you to explore
            There's nothing but miracles beyond your door
            The Dark Carnival is your invitation
            To witness them without explanation
            Take a look at this fine creation
            And enjoy it better with appreciation
            Crows, ghosts, the midnight coast
            The wonders of the world, mysteries the most
            Just open your mind, and it ain't no way
            To ignore the miracles of every day

            (Are you a firm believer in miracles)
            Magic everywhere in this bitch
            (Do you notice and recognize miracles)
            It's all around you, you don't even know it
            (Are you a firm believer in miracles)
            Magic everywhere in this bitch
            Shit's crazy
            (Do you notice and recognize miracles,
            So many miracles, the magic miracles)

            Are you a firm believer in miracles
            Do you have time for the miracles
            Do you notice and recognize miracles
            So many miracles, the magic miracles
            Are you a firm believer in miracles
            Do you have time for the miracles
            Do you notice and recognize miracles
            So many miracles, the magic miracles
            Are you a firm believer in miracles
            Do you have time for the miracles
            Do you notice and recognize miracles
            So many miracles, the magic miracles
            Are you a firm believer in miracles
            Do you have time for the miracles
            Do you notice and recognize miracles
            So many miracles, the magic miracles        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I heard X about ASPECT, why is the witch ignoring it.
        </header>
        <body>
            Because witches are weird man, haven't you ever read a fairy tale?
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why did the witch just did the most draw dropping shit i have ever seen and completely changed the session, why isn't she doing that on a regular basis?
        </header>
        <body>
            Ever seen in fairy tales how witches rewrite the story and all it's rules then kinda are irrelevant? It's like that.
            Mechanically witches have a second hidden pluck bar which is HUGE like 1000x what it should, but they can only tap it when it's like 2-300+x their normal bar and it only fills up from overflow of their normal bar.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Hey, where is the Void pla- OHGOD
        </header>
        <body>
            Did they just appear right behind you? Thought so.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why do I hear angry and loud voices in my head?
        </header>
        <body>
            Just Exiles. You probably gave them a bad impression. Or the Caps-Lock is on.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why is the rage player already God-Tier? I've only just entered the game.
        </header>
        <body>
            giggle-snort
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: The ghost puppet thing won't shut up! How do I make it stop!
        </header>
        <body>
            You don't. So unless you can get the Time player to jump in the Kernal for you, you're stuck with that horrible abomination.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: why do i keep dying to a giant snake?
        </header>
        <body>
            Thats called a denizen,and maybe you should abscond befere you have a Unlucky Br8k
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: It keeps happening!
        </header>
        <body>
            I warned you about the stairs bro!
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: My friend just went crazy! I think they want to kill me! Oh God Oh God Oh God Oh-
        </header>
        <body>
            Shut up. There are two ways to deal with this, either calm their asses down or put their asses down
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What does that mean?
        </header>
        <body>
            Either get them to calm down or kill them before they kill you.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: That's terrible!
        </header>
        <body>
            Deal with it.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What's this Swirly Lollipop?
        </header>
        <body>
            Put it down. Just put it down.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: There are things... in the sky, or not the sky? Whatever it there are things, whispering things above, err below? Things around Derse, just what are they?
        </header>
        <body>
            Don't worry about it.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: But-
        </header>
        <body>
            No, just no. They less you know the better.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What are you doing?
        </header>
        <body>
            Making chocolate pudding.
        </body>
        <header>
            Question: Why on earth are you making chocolate pudding at 4 in the morning?
        </header>
        <body>
            Because I've lost control of my life.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Are you losing control over your life?
        </header>
        <body>
            Yes.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            yo how do i grind up that wicked verballistamina
        </header>
        <body>
            you gotta get absolutely NOIDED at the verbullshitstick crazytoriumhouse my dude
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            The robot went murdermode! What do I do?!
        </header>
        <body>
            What kind of man builds a machine to kill a kid? No, he did not use his hands; like a smart man, he used a tool...
            But just the same! Can you question who's to blame?
            My advice is to put it down immediately!
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Can I kick it?
        </header>
        <body>
            Yes you can!
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What is the purple frog.
        </header>
        <body>
            The frog is the lotus of your session, it symbolizes your creation. The purple lotus represents openness to enlightenment, by seeking the purple frog you are showing the enlightenment offered by the horror terrors.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why is the purple frog trying to kill me?!
        </header>
        <body>
            It merely seeks to liberate you from your physical form that you may further your enlightenement in dream bubbles, unlike other dead you shall continue to grow.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How do you get the Purple frog?
        </header>
        <body>
            -100% Frog breeding.
        </body>
    </section>




</faq>