<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <ascii>

    </ascii>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How bullshit is this game?
        </header>
        <body>
            100%
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            glub?
        </header>
        <body>
            blub 38D
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            My friend prototyped a 'horrorterror', and now they aren't responding!
        </header>
        <body>
            Calm them down RIGHT NOW, or else you're going to be screwed later on.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            My friend prototyped a 'horrorterror', and now they aren't responding!
        </header>
        <body>
            they have a new huggable friend :D
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            im hearing voices from the 'furthest ring', whats their deal?
        </header>
        <body>
            tangle buddies!!!! W,,,,W :hugging::hugging::sparkling_heart::sparkling_heart::squid::squid:
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Oh god the horrorterrors do NOT want to be tangle buddies...
        </header>
        <body>
            Oh, they do.  They want to tangle you in their tentacles and erode your mind and soul, feeding on your decaying psyche.  They want to crack open the game like an egg and suck out the innards, i.e. you.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What do the horrorterrors want with me!?
        </header>
        <body>
            They just want to help you. The only way to save your friends is by defying the game. By breaking it.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Oh god the horrorterrors do NOT want to be tangle buddies...
        </header>
        <body>
            Oh, they do.  They want to tangle you in their tentacles and give you lots of hugs!! They want to say glub lots and be nice friends!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            The Horrorterrors touched me and now my friends can't understand a word I say...
        </header>
        <body>
            What was that?
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            The Horrorterrors touched me and now my friends can't understand a word I say...
        </header>
        <body>
            enjoy your cute new cuttle friends :D
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            What to do if one of your players has stopped responding to messages.
        </header>
        <body>
            First, ask around to make sure it's not just you.  (If it is, you should probably apologize for whatever you said. Communication is vital to your survival here, and way more important than your pride.) If the player isn't responding to anyone at all, TREAT THIS AS AN EMERGENCY SITUATION. Have their server player track them down, if possible. If not, have anyone who can get to their Land searching for them as soon as possible.

            Self-isolation is one of the early symptoms of exposure to certain negative influences that can not only kill that player, but derail your entire session, possibly badly enough to kill everyone in the session. Take this very seriously.
        </body>
    </section>


</faq>