<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
<ascii>

</ascii>

    <section>
    <header>
        Question: How bullshit is SBURBSim?
    </header>
    <body>
        Extremely.
    </body>
</section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What are Players?
        </header>
        <body>
            Faceless dolls who communicate entirely through failing the turing test.

            Oh.

            Wait.

            You were serious. Uh.

            Players are...the people who play SBURB?
        </body>
    </section>

    
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: HOW DO YOU SOLVE [???]!!!!"!1!!!!!ONE!!!ELEVENTWELVE
        </header>
        <body>
            the answer is [insert gigglesnort here]
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Where is everything better than expected?
        </header>
        <body>
            Holy shit, I'm not just going to TELL you. It's a myserty.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            The consorts say I have the Denizen.... JavaScript?  What is up with that.
        </header>
        <body>
            console.log("I sure hope you like typos!")

            console.log("Because the Denizen JavaScript is gonna be full of them");

            console.log("And you get to spend a bullshit amount of time finding all of them before you can even BEGIN to fight your true Denizen.")

            if(player.aspect == "Viod") console.log("But at least whole sections of your denizens quests can never even happen.")

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Apparently I have the Denizen....  Hair7?
        </header>
        <body>
            JR Hacks the FAQ:  Lololool.

            Okay.   Hold on. Let me just....take over for a bit.

            Hair7 is my personal nemesis, enshrined as a Denizen for all time. It is the stupidest possible bug, and yet it keeps coming back.  I accidentally archived Nepeta's hair as 'Hair7.png" and not "hair7.png" and no amount of effort and yelling could convince the archive to remember the true name for very long.

            And yes.  Nepeta breaking the sim is canon. AB's irrational hatred is justified.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            My denizen is Yaldabaoth?
        </header>
        <body>
            Congrats, you got the hardest possible denizen tier, it doesn't even relate to your aspect. Good luck!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: What is "Duthulu"? </header> <body> Shit! Who told you about that!? I... I mean uh. There is no such thing and anyone you tells you different is insane and likely to go Murder Mode any minute. I advise you to kill them as quickly as possible. Multiple times. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: Hey can you give me PR3M1UM gigglesnort? </header> <body> No </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: I beat my Denizen, have I beat the game? </header> <body> No, hell no. Even if your session went better than most then you still have two eldritch monstrosities to fight! And if you found this FAQ then you are definitely not in one of those sessions. So prepare for the next ultimate boss fight, the next monster will actually want to win. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why are these FAQs being made?
        </header>
        <body>
            Not much else to do in a null session, is there?
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What's the answer to [???]?
        </header>
        <body>
            "Shit, hell if I know
        </body>
    </section>


    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What is the answer to ???
        </header>
        <body>
            That's a secret, my dude
        </body>
    </section>


    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Where is everything better than expected?
        </header>
        <body>
            Holy shit, I'm not just going to TELL you. It's a myserty.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section><header> Question: ???</header> <body>!!!</body></section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: My denizen is just a title what do i do?!?!
        </header>
        <body>
            Answer: [Critical Threat] You know how Wastes lack restraint? Well, JR and PL kinda sorta got into the source code of the game and added something a little... narcissistic in.  KR, of course, was pissed as hell.  These denizens are POWERFUL.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
    <header>How many Player has JR killed?</header>
    <body>Sextillions</body>
</section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What is the pink frog?
        </header>
        <body>
            The frog is the lotus of your session , a thing a sacred beauty formed from the muck of you and your dumb society. The pink lotus is the perfected lotus, were your frog to be a pink frog it would then be a perfect universe. I do not believe such a thing is possible.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Quirks
        </header>
        <body>
            Turns out they definitely affect FAQs.
            The quick brown fox jumped over the lazy dog and shit happened too.
            See?
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What is the current exchange of Minecraft Diamonds to Boondollars?
        </header>
        <body>
            About 100 Boondollars for one diamond
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Um. What was "The Great Refactoring"?
        </header>
        <body>
            Apparently SBURB used to be written in JavaScript, which let it get away with some sick nasty shit.  At some point one of the MetaPlayers decided that JavaScript was too much of a giant piece of shit, so they converted everything to a different language.

            This set all sessions on fire for awhile (sucks to be them), and then  afterwards the timelines were WAY more stable.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Who is "The AuthorBot"?
        </header>
        <body>
            Every so often sessions have this weird robot show up.  She doesn't seem to do anything, she just watches, and if you go up to her, she'll say something about not being allowed to alter timelines.

            That said, I HAVE heard that sometimes meteors reign down on anybody who messes with her? Better to stay away.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Who is "AuthorBotJunior"?
        </header>
        <body>
            Uh.

            Fuck.

            Okay.

            Like.

            Don't Panic.

            But.

            You're fucked. You are so fucked.  Sessions only have the little girl scout robot show up if they are beyond saving. I'm talking total party wipe, do not pass go do not collect 200 dollars.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Why doesn't anyone have a face?
        </header>
        <body>
            What's a "face"???
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Why do we have no faces?
        </header>
        <body>
            Because yes
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Who/What is the Author?
        </header>
        <body>
            Depends, for some it's a waste with a yellow stick, for others it's an orange dude with white eyes, some even say that their author is a green kid in red overalls. Experiences between authors vary. Call our support hotline 555-413-1025 for assistance with dealing with them
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            So um, I opened a random session, but everything looks different and some people are just dying randomly, combo sessions are crashing too. What do I do??? D:
        </header>
        <body>
            uh, I'm not sure what you me-

            JR: Oh shit, is this an actual F.A.Q. question? Ok um, if you're encountering this scenario, it means that you've accidentally enabled the experimental branch, which is much less stable and prone to errors. Not to worry though, simply select the Main Branch entry from the drop-down tab at the top and things should be working properly again!

            Who are you and what are you doing in my FA-

            JR: shhh
        </body>
    </section>

</faq>