<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
<ascii>

</ascii>

    <section>
    <header>
        Question: How bullshit is SBURBSim?
    </header>
    <body>
        Extremely.
    </body>
</section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What are Players?
        </header>
        <body>
            Faceless dolls who communicate entirely through failing the turing test.

            Oh.

            Wait.

            You were serious. Uh.

            Players are...the people who play SBURB?
        </body>
    </section>

    
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: HOW DO YOU SOLVE [???]!!!!"!1!!!!!ONE!!!ELEVENTWELVE
        </header>
        <body>
            the answer is [insert gigglesnort here]
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Where is everything better than expected?
        </header>
        <body>
            Holy shit, I'm not just going to TELL you. It's a myserty.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            The consorts say I have the Denizen.... JavaScript?  What is up with that.
        </header>
        <body>
            console.log("I sure hope you like typos!")

            console.log("Because the Denizen JavaScript is gonna be full of them");

            console.log("And you get to spend a bullshit amount of time finding all of them before you can even BEGIN to fight your true Denizen.")

            if(player.aspect == "Viod") console.log("But at least whole sections of your denizens quests can never even happen.")

        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Apparently I have the Denizen....  Hair7?
        </header>
        <body>
            JR Hacks the FAQ:  Lololool.

            Okay.   Hold on. Let me just....take over for a bit.

            Hair7 is my personal nemesis, enshrined as a Denizen for all time. It is the stupidest possible bug, and yet it keeps coming back.  I accidentally archived Nepeta's hair as 'Hair7.png" and not "hair7.png" and no amount of effort and yelling could convince the archive to remember the true name for very long.

            And yes.  Nepeta breaking the sim is canon. AB's irrational hatred is justified.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            My denizen is Yaldabaoth?
        </header>
        <body>
            Congrats, you got the hardest possible denizen tier, it doesn't even relate to your aspect. Good luck!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: What is "Duthulu"? </header> <body> Shit! Who told you about that!? I... I mean uh. There is no such thing and anyone you tells you different is insane and likely to go Murder Mode any minute. I advise you to kill them as quickly as possible. Multiple times. </body> </section>

</faq>