<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Bards.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why do my god tier clothes make me look like a clown?
        </header>
        <body>
            Answer: They do say you are what you wear. Embrace the clown.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            I'm supposedly a bard. What exactly does that mean?
        </header>
        <body>
            Everything's backwards, bro. You suck at what you're supposed to be good at and you excel at whatever you're supposed to be bad at. Stand proud, use those sticks and stones to build a castle or some shit.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section> <header> Screw this crap why am I the clown. </header> <body> Being the bard doesn't mean you're literally the clown.  One thing it means is you can destroy your aspect in yourself and others.  Like, let's say you're the bard of life and you see this guy just ignoring all the rules and trying to power through all their quests on strength alone that's totally going to get themselves killed for being a dumbass.  Well, it's your job to spray them with water and say down boy.  And no I am not talking about anyone in particular, VICTOR.</body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            ....What's a 'Bard'?
        </header>
        <body>
            Well, Bards tell stories right? They are never the star but they usually cause everything.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why are my consorts acting like a 'Bard' is a bad ass?
        </header>
        <body>
            Because a Bard is one of the two destroy classes in SBURB. Just roll with it.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I'm a Bard. Am I expected to play a lute and wear poofy pants or some shit?
        </header>
        <body>
            Nope, you're expected to destroy your session from within and have a giant cod piece. You can remove it right after getting god tier though.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Bard. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Make things end. Or be an asshole. Your choice.
        </body>
    </section>

</faq>