<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Heirs.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Apparently I'm a Heir? Does that mean somebody in this weird place left my a bunch of money? </header> <body> No, you gotta earn your boonbucks like everyone else. However you will literally inherit the powers and traits of your Aspect. Don't worry about what that means and just keep on doing the things you do, you'll figure it out when you're meant too. Just be thankful you got a simple, usually-not-a-instant-lose Class! </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            So, I'm an Heir, right? So how and where do I actually get my powers and aspect stuff?
        </header>
        <body>
            It's really hard to say, honestly. Sometimes you can gain your aspect from Skaia, from denizens, or from your fellow players. An Heir is "one who inherits [x]", but it's never really specified where you inherit [x] from. I guess when coming up with the Heir class, Skaia was literally just like, "Eh, I don't care how you inherit it, just inherit it!"
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> They keep calling me an Heir, what's that? </header> <body> Just chill, and pay attention to what goes on around you.  Sometimes you'll notice your aspect doing stuff and it'll seem way too convenient.  It's not.  The convenient is you.</body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Uh, I'm an 'Heir' right? What am I supposed to inherit?
        </header>
        <body>
            The second part of your title. You're an Heir of X, where X is Doom or Time or whatever.   Expect that to just sort of work out for you.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            These weird coincidences keep following me everywhere.
        </header>
        <body>
            Sshhhhhhhh..... Don't talk about it. Try not to think about it. DEFINITELY don't take it for granted. Just...enjoy it while it lasts.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why don't any of these consorts know who I am?
        </header>
        <body>
            You know in a movie where there's some long lost Heir and they show up out of nowhere to claim their birthright, but before they do they travel incognito and scope shit out?  Yup, that's you.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Heir. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Grow up and lead your team to victory.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>