<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Knights.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Wait, what's this about frogs?
        </header>
        <body>
            Either you're the Space player, or a Knight.  Space player breeds the Frogs, Knight basically does a game long escort quest to help out.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            My friends keep dying, how am I supposed to be protecting them?
        </header>
        <body>
            Generally, the best way to protect your friends while playing SBURB is through whatever your aspect is.  Breath or Time or whatever the fuck.  Do a few quests on your planet and you'll get a feel for how it works.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Uh, I heard that the Knight was supposed to help me breed frogs, but *I* am the Knight.
        </header>
        <body>
            Oh man, sucks to be you, dude.   Looks like you're on your own. Good luck!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Where does SBURB even come up with these shitty classes? What even IS a Knight?
        </header>
        <body>
            I'm pretty sure it's like, narrative archetypes and shit.  Knights quest and protect and slay beasts and stuff.  Try doing that kind of stuff.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            WHY THE FUCK ARE THERE SO MANY QUESTS ON MY PLANET?
        </header>
        <body>
            Welcome to Knighthood, bro.  Quests are just something Knights do.  Get ready to help the Space player, too. Quests for days.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I really fucking hate the Space Player.
        </header>
        <body>
            Suck it up.  Without them, you can't beat the game. Just try to ignore them and get their quests out of the way as fast as possible.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Knight. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Go punch enemies in the snout. And probably check on the Space player once in a while.
        </body>
    </section>

</faq>