<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Mages.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: So a Mage is a wizard? I'm now a wizard? </header> <body> Yer a Wizard 'Arry Noooooot Exactly. See this is where things get tough. Supposedly Mage is the counterpart to Seer which means you would be an understanding class. Of course it also could be the counterpa.... You know what? Mages basically have an understanding of the aspect and learn through it. Yes it might require some self sacrifice but you get to be the knowledge badass when it comes to your aspect. So yeah you're pretty rad. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> I just saw my friends die! But like...not infront of me in like the future? </header> <body> Welcome to the wonderful world of prophechy, that's what will happen if you don't make diffrent choices. So go save them. Also whatever you just saw still happens but in an alternate timeline where everyone dies because by changing it you make it inconsistent, but leave that to your time player to worry about. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: My co-players keep complaining about me being too good at this game. Is it because I am a Mage? </header> <body> You're goddamned right. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I heard that Mage's suffer?
        </header>
        <body>
            Some do, some don't.  It's more that Mages sort of have all of their aspect stronger, both the good and the bad parts.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What's the point of a Mage?
        </header>
        <body>
            I've heard a lot of conflicting head canons.  They suffer their aspect, then know their aspect, they have the POWER of their aspect (but not the control).   Do what
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why doesn't anybody listen to me?
        </header>
        <body>
            Because you're probably a Mage, not a Seer.   Seers give the wisdom of their aspects to others, while Mages are supposed to keep it for themself.  SBURB just won't cut you a break if you try to escape your role.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Mage. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Suffer from headaches and spew cryptic yet very useful advice.
        </body>
    </section>

</faq>