<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Maids.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section> <header> Question: I am a Maid so what now ? </header> <body> A Maid? Well from what I understand a Maid of [Aspect] is one who creates/organises their Aspect.They will serve their Aspect but in doing so eventually...sort of have have their Aspect's Will in their Doing ? It is Complicated.Either way they(and you) also Embrace their Aspect,all the parts of it,like all the good and bad stuff. </body> </section>
    <header>
        How can I best show my friends and enemies what I'm MAID of?
    </header>
    <body>
        Nice pun. But seriously, remember you can create your aspect, and that aspects are more then their literal interpretations e.g. Breath and Freedom.
    </body>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why are my quests so boring?
        </header>
        <body>
            I bet you're a Maid.  Maids get to do various things that serve their aspect, up until they are high enough level to SERVE their aspect to their enemies on a silver plate of whoop ass.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What's up with these leg wrappings? How are they "Maid"?
        </header>
        <body>
            Hey, if you have ever seen the weirder costumes, you would not be complaining.  The wrappings look cool!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            If I'm the Maid of X, why is everybody else so much more full of X than normal?
        </header>
        <body>
            As a Maid, you serve your aspect to your friends.  You get some along with, but it's mostly something you give to others.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Maid. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Serve your Aspect to others as the Best Butler Ever.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>