<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How bullshit are Pages.
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            My consorts keep telling me I am shit.
        </header>
        <body>
            Welcome to Pagehood, where you have to EARN your right to not suck at this game.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Whoa, I started to get REALLY good at this game all of a sudden.
        </header>
        <body>
            You're probably a Page then.  Pages start out sucking, and are forced to Apprentice to other players or consorts or whatever, but once you put in the time you get to be a fucking god at your aspect.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            A consort wants to join up with me, but when I said 'yes', he froze.  What gives?
        </header>
        <body>
            Yeah, SBURB is kind of a piece of shit, buggy, unfinished game.  Consort companions haven't been implemented yet in your version.  Other versions might have it though, who knows.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            People keep making "blank page" jokes around me and I'm getting really tired of it.
        </header>
        <body>
            Oh man, are you a Page of Void?  Hilarious.   Other gems include Heir of Breath, Knight of Light, Knight of Time, Witch of Space.....it just goes on.

            SBURB is a shitty, punny game.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            My sprite/consorts keep talking about "Apprenticing".  What's that?
        </header>
        <body>
            Basically, Pages aren't really allowed to do much on their own.  You have to hook up with another player (or an NPC, if you're version of SBURB is more complete than mine) in order to get anything done.  You basically won't even be able to do quests without being Apprenticed.

            The process is pretty easy, though.   Just hang out with someone else and let them take the lead.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Oh God.
        </header>
        <body>
            Yeah.  Yeah.  I hear ya buddy.

            Those godtier pants SUCK.

            Just try to pretend you're a sidekick.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Page. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Help others to punch enemies in the snout. Then carry the team to victory.
        </body>
    </section>

</faq>