<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How bullshit are Princes.
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Why do my consorts seem to be so afraid of me?
        </header>
        <body>
            Welcome to Princehood!  As a "Destroyer" class you have a big bad rep to live up to/destroy utterly when you turn out to be a weenie.  Good luck!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Wait...I am supposed to destroy my Aspect?
        </header>
        <body>
            Well, it's not as simple as that.  Sure, you can go that route and end up the exact opposite of whatever the usual Hero of X is, but you can also destroy WITH your Aspect, and sort of embrace everything about it.

            You'd think it would be useful to have such a broad role, but it really only ends up being annoying as fuck without direction.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I don't feel very much like a Prince.
        </header>
        <body>
            There's two main schools of thought here:

            1)  You don't know shit about what Princes are, and you actually really do fit it

            or

            2)  SBURB is gonna make you into a Prince whether you like it or not.

            Enjoy!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            ... Are these poofy asshole pants REALLY necessary?
        </header>
        <body>
            I've heard rumors that you can change up the god tier outfits, but have never found a way yet.  Just embrace the pants.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What's with this headband thing?
        </header>
        <body>
            It's like....a cloth tiara.  Cuz you're a prince. Do princes even WEAR tiaras?  Has SBURB even ever seen a Prince?  The questions are endless.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: If a prince awakes in a forest and there's no shit to hear them, is it still wrecked?
        </header>
        <body>
            Definitely.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Prince. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Learn how to End Things. Ride in. Kill the monster and make out with its captive. Or make out with the monster, who cares.
        </body>
    </section>


</faq>