<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Rogues.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            So someone called me a Rogue, wha-
        </header>
        <body>
            Dear Duthulu! Yes! Rouges are awesome! Rogues are universally sexy and adventurous and always totally adorable! You are now literally Robin Hood, but better! You steal shit from the various horrible monsters and incomprehensible forces in your session then give them to others! You are legitimately a smuggler of magic, you're Han Solo, but magic! Your Aspect determines what goods you steal and redistribute, but regardless of your Aspect you'll get really cool powers! Anyway, Rogues are awesome!
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            Question: This game is stupid! I'm not getting any of my powers as fast as my friends are! What gives?
        </header>
        <body>
            It's likely you're either a Thief or a Rogue. Naturally, this means you will only ever receive very little of your aspect naturally. You are forced to take it from others. For some people that might sound a little too harsh, but that's why you have your maturity quests. Learn to love stealing. You'll need it.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How do I even steal these aspects anyway?
        </header>
        <body>
            You need to think outside of the literal definition of each aspect and start thinking figuratively. Every aspect has a meaning less literal than it implies. You will become much of effective when you start stealing abstract concepts.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Why doesn't stealing from underlings give me all the power I wanted?
        </header>
        <body>
            Steal from everyone. Players, consorts, carapacians, anyone you can think of. Stealing isn't always a bad thing. All aspects have the potential for positive and negative interpretation. When you steal the negative interpretation of your aspect, you can almost see it as healing.

            In short, don't be afraid to steal from your friends.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Whenever I try to steal something, it just seems to float off into the air and vanish. Why can't I use it?
        </header>
        <body>
            That's because you're a Rogue. You're not meant to use any of what you steal. You're supposed to take so that you can give to others. Sort of like Robin Hood.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: I stole something myself! I deserve to keep it!
        </header>
        <body>
            Get busy giving or get busy dying.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: What's the coolest way to exploit being a Rogue?
        </header>
        <body>
            Give either an Imp or a Consort something that you stole. Then steal it again and give it back. Do this over and over again to grind levels. It's tedious, but so is almost everything else in this stupid game.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: Where do I keep my pillaged loot once I'm out of space?
        </header>
        <body>
            Seeing how the Rogue is a passive class, you'll want to bring a few friends with you. Whether they're Consorts or other Players does not matter. Have them pick up all your loot and let them keep it. This is incredibly useful for completing quests that involve giving a certain number of stolen objects to other people.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Rogue. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Steal shit. Share what others want, keep what you need.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>