<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Seers.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: Why do these other players keep nagging me about seemingly trivial nonsense? </header> <body> Chances are, you're the Seer or Sylph of the session, which means you basically have to herd your little flock to victory... lest they be caught in the theoretical jaws of the wolf. Their death is the exact opposite of what you need, as you need all the power you can muster to survive your session. If they try killing you, however, killing them instead is a free action. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question:why do i sometimes know Stuff ? </header> <body> You are a Seer </body> </section>
    <section> <header> I just saw my friends die! But like...not infront of me in like the future? </header> <body> Welcome to the wonderful world of prophechy, that's what will happen if you don't make diffrent choices. So go save them. Also whatever you just saw still happens but in an alternate timeline where everyone dies because by changing it you make it inconsistent, but leave that to your time player to worry about. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I'm a Seer. Does that mean I'm not supposed to fight
        </header>
        <body>
            Nah, everybody fights in SBURB. Get used to having indirect attacks though, like weird lasers.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Um. I'm a Seer of a something that is NOT something that makes sense.
        </header>
        <body>
            Eh, you'll figure it out. Plenty of aspects have non-literal interpretations, and you'd be surprised how much even literal interpretations can be "seen". Use your imagination.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Um. How am I supposed to be a Seer if I'm blind?
        </header>
        <body>
            Actually, you're fitting your role VERY well at this point.  SBURB LOVES blinding it's Seers. Some sort of irony fetish. Don't worry, you will only get better at metaphorically seeing.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Seer. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Tell others that doing X will probably do them in.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>