<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Sylph.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: Why do these other players keep nagging me about seemingly trivial nonsense? </header> <body> Chances are, you're the Seer or Sylph of the session, which means you basically have to herd your little flock to victory... lest they be caught in the theoretical jaws of the wolf. Their death is the exact opposite of what you need, as you need all the power you can muster to survive your session. If they try killing you, however, killing them instead is a free action. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Some ghost thing called me a Sylph? What is that? Did the ghost of my dead pet insult me! </header> <body> No, unless your dead dog is a misogynist. A Sylph is one of the twelve Classes of Sburb, the game you are playing now. Sylphs are passive magic users, meaning when you start reaching your full potential you'll get all sorts of healing magic and various buffs you can use to help your friends. But its going to be a while before you reach that point. So just focus on doing quests and shit, most of them are gonna involve helping your Consorts. As an interesting side note, all Sylphs are female, or the closest your species has. They are quite helpful and very nice and they genuinely care for others, hence the focus on healing magic to the detriment to offensive magic. Though if you are a guy then your dead goldfish is just giving you a hard time. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I heard that Sylphs are just more magical Witches?
        </header>
        <body>
            You're not wrong.  While Witches gain power from being around others, Sylphs strengthen those they spend time around.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why is everyone so much stronger than me?
        </header>
        <body>
            Because a Sylphs power is to  health their aspect in those they spend time with.  Looks like you're quite popular.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            What the hell is a Sylph?
        </header>
        <body>
            Like a magical forest creature? I dunno man. SBURB is weird.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Sylph. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Meddle with and assist other players. And probably majyyk enemies in the snouts.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>