<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How bullshit are Thieves.
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> All my consorts keep calling me a thief, but I didn't even steal from them! Well not yet at least. </header> <body> Thief is the rest of your SBURB title. You remember how they also called you the "Hero of [Thing]?" Replace "hero" with Thief and there you go. As a Thief, you relocate your aspect (the [Thing] if you haven't already guessed that.) Mostly, you will be relocating inwards, in other words stealing it, but you also have the power to give. But lol why would you want to give, all of that [Thing] is rightfully yours! </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Are the consorts' banks supposed to be this easy to rob?
        </header>
        <body>
            Just take it, man, you're only the richer for it.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Hey, uh, I get the feeling that these FAQs are just sort of being thrown together randomly.
        </header>
        <body>
            Welcome to the wonderful world of meta. You enjoy being a Waste, I take it?
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why do all my consorts keep talking about the Cataclysm I am going to cause?
        </header>
        <body>
            Wastes fuck shit up.  "Lay Waste to" in other words.  Good luck trying to steer that shit into not fucking over your own party too much.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Holy fuck I keep leveling up but all that happens is I get slightly better at strifes.  My friends are getting all sorts of weird abilities. What gives?
        </header>
        <body>
            I'd be you're a Waste. Wastes 'waste' their aspect, until it's time to 'lay waste with' it. Try to just enjoy it while it lasts, you'll be nostalgic for this shit before you know it.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>