<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            Question: How bullshit are Thieves.
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> All my consorts keep calling me a thief, but I didn't even steal from them! Well not yet at least. </header> <body> Thief is the rest of your SBURB title. You remember how they also called you the "Hero of [Thing]?" Replace "hero" with Thief and there you go. As a Thief, you relocate your aspect (the [Thing] if you haven't already guessed that.) Mostly, you will be relocating inwards, in other words stealing it, but you also have the power to give. But lol why would you want to give, all of that [Thing] is rightfully yours! </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Are the consorts' banks supposed to be this easy to rob?
        </header>
        <body>
            Just take it, man, you're only the richer for it.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            I feel like I'm ....missing something after spending some time with my friend.
        </header>
        <body>
            Chance are they were a Thief. Thieves don't MEAN to, but do take their aspect from those around them. Thems the Breaks.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            This is bullshit, why am I so weak?
        </header>
        <body>
            I'm gonna guess that you're a Thief or a Rogue and you haven't been spending much time around other players.   You can't steal shit if you aren't around people, after all.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Am I a bad person because I'm a Thief?
        </header>
        <body>
            Not at all!  There's plenty of things you can steal from your friends that leaves them better off, though it does require you to be worse off in exchange.  Try to focus on the negative aspects of your... well, aspect!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Thief. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Steal shit. Keep what you want, share what others need.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>