<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Wastes.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Im a waste of time!!!!! </header> <body> Yes you are </body> </section>
    <section>
    <header>
        My friend seems to really like messing up the code of this game! What are they even doing? I don't understand!
    </header>
    <body>That is what tends to happen when people know enough about the game. Is your friend a Waste? If so, really not surprised here. When somebody understands the programming behind SBURB, they really just can't resist trying to break it. Could you? That's what I thought.
    </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Hey, uh, I get the feeling that these FAQs are just sort of being thrown together randomly.
        </header>
        <body>
            Welcome to the wonderful world of meta. You enjoy being a Waste, I take it?
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Why do all my consorts keep talking about the Cataclysm I am going to cause?
        </header>
        <body>
            Wastes fuck shit up.  "Lay Waste to" in other words.  Good luck trying to steer that shit into not fucking over your own party too much.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Holy fuck I keep leveling up but all that happens is I get slightly better at strifes.  My friends are getting all sorts of weird abilities. What gives?
        </header>
        <body>
            I'd be you're a Waste. Wastes 'waste' their aspect, until it's time to 'lay waste with' it. Try to just enjoy it while it lasts, you'll be nostalgic for this shit before you know it.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Waste. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Probably take a peek at the code. What could possibly go wrong?
        </body>
    </section>

</faq>