<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<faq>
    <section>
        <header>
            +++++++++++++++++++++Question: How bullshit are Witches.+++++++++++++++++++++++
        </header>
        <body>
            Extremely.
        </body>
    </section>
    <section> <header> Question: I'm a Witch. What do I do? Do I like... make potions and get burned at a stake or something? </header> <body> Witches are what I like to call Magical Problem Solvers. You'll get magic, then you'll get shit done. </body> </section> <section> <header> Question: Help! I don't have any magic! </header> <body> You'll get your flashy majjiks when you're good and damn ready. Just focus on your "Self Actualization" and commune with you Aspect and do quests and shit. And for the love of Duthulu don't kill anyone. </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: The Witch just-just... MURDERED one of my friends! They were starting to act a little strange, the Witch said they needed to be dealt with, and then they just KILLED THEM! </header> <body> Yeah, Witches are problem solvers. However they tend to be a little...heavy handed. So if your friend was going Murder Mode or GrimDark then yeah. The Witch "solved" the problem
    </body> </section>
    <section> <header> Question: The Witch keeps flat out ignoring my Seer, and keeps doing all the things they say aren't possible. </header> <body> You know the saying "Rules are meant to be broken"? Witches sure do. </body> </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Oh god I didn't mean to prototype that!
        </header>
        <body>
            Enjoy your new familiar ;)
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Huh. I don't feel very in tune with my aspect.  Like, I understand some parts of it, but others seem to be really wrong?
        </header>
        <body>
            Enjoy being a witch!
        </body>
    </section>
    <section>
        <header>
            Wow, I feel REALLY good! I spent a lot of time helping a friend out with quests and it's like I am WAY higher level or something? What gives?
        </header>
        <body>
            That would be the "coven" boost Witches get.  Being around other people just gives you a boost to your Aspect, that's all.
        </body>
    </section>

    <section>
        <header>
            It seems that I have rolled Witch. What should I do?
        </header>
        <body>
            Grab your familiar and go majyyk enemies in the snouts.
        </body>
    </section>
</faq>